<doc><field name="id">6201</field><field name="title">google-guetzli</field><field name="session">Using</field><field name="sentence">While it will work on otherimages too, results will be poorer</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6202</field><field name="title">google-guetzli</field><field name="session">Using</field><field name="sentence">You can try compressing an enclosed  samplehigh qualityimage You can pass a --quality Q parameter to set quality in units equivalent tolibjpeg quality</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6203</field><field name="title">google-guetzli</field><field name="session">Using</field><field name="sentence">You can also pass a --verbose flag to see a trace of encodingattempts made.Please note that JPEG images do not support alpha channel  transparency</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6204</field><field name="title">google-guetzli</field><field name="session">Using</field><field name="sentence">If theinput is a PNG with an alpha channel, it will be overlaid on black backgroundbefore encoding.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6205</field><field name="title">google-guice-aqueduct</field><field name="session">Guice Aqueduct</field><field name="sentence">Guice Aqueduct is a Guice binder to configure Chained instances to form a pipeline</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6206</field><field name="title">google-guice-aqueduct</field><field name="session">Guice Aqueduct</field><field name="sentence">For each Chained item, next in pipeline will be set via Chained.setNext call at injection time</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6207</field><field name="title">google-guice-aqueduct</field><field name="session">Guice Aqueduct</field><field name="sentence">For the last item in line, noOp instance configured from the constructor will be set as the next item.For example, suppose we have a Chained pipeline class:abstract class Pipeline implements Chained {  Pipeline next;  public void setNext Pipeline next  {  }class PipelineA extends Pipeline {  @Override  void process   {  }class PipelineB extends Pipeline {  @Override  void process   {  }class NoOpPipeline extends Pipeline {  @Override  void process   {  }Now, when we inject a pipeline through the following calls inside a module:Note that instead of implementing Chained.setNext, one could extend AbstractPipeline which does the same thing as what Pipeline class does in the example above.Disclaimer: This is not an official Google product.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6208</field><field name="title">google-gulava</field><field name="session">Gulava</field><field name="sentence">*Relational programming library for Java.*Gulava allows you to write relational predicates in Java</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6209</field><field name="title">google-gulava</field><field name="session">Gulava</field><field name="sentence">You can writeProlog-style predicates and use them from normal Java code, seamlesslyintegrated with the magic of annotation processors.See the  GitHub wiki  for some how-tos and to get started writing your own predicates and logic value types.This repository requires  Bazel  to build,test, and run</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6210</field><field name="title">google-gulava</field><field name="session">Gulava</field><field name="sentence">After you have set up Bazel, you can run the demo:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6211</field><field name="title">google-gulava</field><field name="session">Contributing</field><field name="sentence">Gulava doesn't have a particular long-term goal in mind besides exploringrelational programming</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6212</field><field name="title">google-gulava</field><field name="session">Contributing</field><field name="sentence">Any contributions to that end are welcome! That could besomething like:MicroKanren paper:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6213</field><field name="title">google-gumbo-parser</field><field name="session">#include "gumbo.h"</field><field name="sentence">int main   {  GumboOutput  // Do stuff with output->root  gumbo_destroy_output &kGumboDefaultOptions, output ;See the API documentation and sample programs for more details.A note on API/ABI compatibilityWe'll make a best effort to preserve API compatibility between releases.The initial release is a 0.9  beta  release to solicit comments from earlyadopters, but if no major problems are found with the API, a 1.0 releasewill follow shortly, and the API of that should be considered stable</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6214</field><field name="title">google-gumbo-parser</field><field name="session">#include "gumbo.h"</field><field name="sentence">Ifchanges are necessary, we follow  semantic versioning   .We make no such guarantees about the ABI, and it's very likely thatsubsequent versions may require a recompile of client code</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6215</field><field name="title">google-gumbo-parser</field><field name="session">#include "gumbo.h"</field><field name="sentence">For thisreason, we recommend NOT using Gumbo data structures throughout a program,and instead limiting them to a translation layer that picks out whateverdata is needed from the parse tree and then converts that to persistentdata structures more appropriate for the application</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6216</field><field name="title">google-gumbo-parser</field><field name="session">#include "gumbo.h"</field><field name="sentence">The API isstructured to encourage this use, with a single delete function for thewhole parse tree, and is not designed with mutation in mind.Python usageTo install the python bindings, make sure that theC library is installed first, and then sudo python setup.py install fromthe root of the distro</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6217</field><field name="title">google-gumbo-parser</field><field name="session">#include "gumbo.h"</field><field name="sentence">This installs a 'gumbo' module; pydoc gumboshould tell you about it.Recommended best-practice for Python usage is to use one of the adapters toan existing API  personally, I prefer BeautifulSoup  and write your programin terms of those</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6218</field><field name="title">google-gumbo-parser</field><field name="session">#include "gumbo.h"</field><field name="sentence">The raw CTypes bindings should be considered buildingblocks for higher-level libraries and rarely referenced directly.External Bindings and other wrappersThe following language bindings or other tools/wrappers are maintained byvarious contributors in other repositories: ruby-gumbo :  nokogumbo :  node-gumbo-parser :  gumbo-d :  lua-gumbo :  OCGumbo :  ObjectiveGumbo :  GumboBindings :  GumboPHP :  Gumbo.jl :  gumbo-libxml :  HTML5 parsing algorithm :  HTML5 spec :  html5lib tests :  googletest :  semantic versioning :  HTML::Gumbo :</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6219</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">gVisor</field><field name="sentence">gVisor is a user-space kernel, written in Go, that implements a substantialportion of the Linux system surface</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6220</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">gVisor</field><field name="sentence">It includes an Open Container Initiative  OCI   oci  runtime called runsc that provides anisolation boundary between the application and the host kernel</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6221</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">gVisor</field><field name="sentence">The runscruntime integrates with Docker and Kubernetes, making it simple to run sandboxedgVisor takes a distinct approach to container sandboxing and makes a differentset of technical trade-offs compared to existing sandbox technologies, thusproviding new tools and ideas for the container security landscape.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6222</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Why does gVisor exist?</field><field name="sentence">Containers are not a  **sandbox**  sandbox</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6223</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Why does gVisor exist?</field><field name="sentence">While containers haverevolutionized how we develop, package, and deploy applications, runninguntrusted or potentially malicious code without additional isolation is not agood idea</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6224</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Why does gVisor exist?</field><field name="sentence">The efficiency and performance gains from using a single, sharedkernel also mean that container escape is possible with a single vulnerability.gVisor is a user-space kernel for containers</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6225</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Why does gVisor exist?</field><field name="sentence">It limits the host kernel surfaceaccessible to the application while still giving the application access to allthe features it expects</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6226</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Why does gVisor exist?</field><field name="sentence">Unlike most kernels, gVisor does not assume or requirea fixed set of physical resources; instead, it leverages existing host kernelfunctionality and runs as a normal user-space process</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6227</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Why does gVisor exist?</field><field name="sentence">In other words, gVisorimplements Linux by way of Linux.gVisor should not be confused with technologies and tools to harden containersagainst external threats, provide additional integrity checks, or limit thescope of access for a service</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6228</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Why does gVisor exist?</field><field name="sentence">One should always be careful about what data ismade available to a container.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6229</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">How is gVisor different from other container isolation mechanisms?</field><field name="sentence">Two other approaches are commonly taken to provide stronger isolation thannative containers.**Machine-level virtualization**, such as  KVM  kvm  and  Xen  xen , exposesvirtualized hardware to a guest kernel via a Virtual Machine Monitor  VMM</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6230</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">How is gVisor different from other container isolation mechanisms?</field><field name="sentence">Thisvirtualized hardware is generally enlightened  paravirtualized  and additionalmechanisms can be used to improve the visibility between the guest and host e.g</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6231</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">How is gVisor different from other container isolation mechanisms?</field><field name="sentence">balloon drivers, paravirtualized spinlocks</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6232</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">How is gVisor different from other container isolation mechanisms?</field><field name="sentence">Running containers indistinct virtual machines can provide great isolation, compatibility andperformance  though nested virtualization may bring challenges in this area ,but for containers it often requires additional proxies and agents, and mayrequire a larger resource footprint and slower start-up times.! Machine-level virtualization  g3doc/Machine-Virtualization.png "Machine-level virtualization" **Rule-based execution**, such as  seccomp  seccomp ,  SELinux  selinux  and AppArmor  apparmor , allows the specification of a fine-grained security policyfor an application or container</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6233</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">How is gVisor different from other container isolation mechanisms?</field><field name="sentence">These schemes typically rely on hooksimplemented inside the host kernel to enforce the rules</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6234</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">How is gVisor different from other container isolation mechanisms?</field><field name="sentence">If the surface can bemade small enough  i.e</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6235</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">How is gVisor different from other container isolation mechanisms?</field><field name="sentence">a sufficiently complete policy defined , then this is anexcellent way to sandbox applications and maintain native performance</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6236</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">How is gVisor different from other container isolation mechanisms?</field><field name="sentence">However,in practice it can be extremely difficult  if not impossible  to reliably definea policy for arbitrary, previously unknown applications, making this approachchallenging to apply universally.! Rule-based execution  g3doc/Rule-Based-Execution.png "Rule-based execution" Rule-based execution is often combined with additional layers forabove.gVisor intercepts application system calls and acts as the guest kernel, withoutthe need for translation through virtualized hardware</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6237</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">How is gVisor different from other container isolation mechanisms?</field><field name="sentence">gVisor may be thought ofas either a merged guest kernel and VMM, or as seccomp on steroids</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6238</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">How is gVisor different from other container isolation mechanisms?</field><field name="sentence">Thisarchitecture allows it to provide a flexible resource footprint  i.e</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6239</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">How is gVisor different from other container isolation mechanisms?</field><field name="sentence">one basedon threads and memory mappings, not fixed guest physical resources  while alsolowering the fixed costs of virtualization</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6240</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">How is gVisor different from other container isolation mechanisms?</field><field name="sentence">However, this comes at the price ofreduced application compatibility and higher per-system call overhead.! gVisor  g3doc/Layers.png "gVisor" On top of this, gVisor employs rule-based execution to provide defense-in-depth details below .gVisor's approach is similar to  User Mode Linux  UML   uml , although UMLvirtualizes hardware internally and thus provides a fixed resource footprint.Each of the above approaches may excel in distinct scenarios</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6241</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">How is gVisor different from other container isolation mechanisms?</field><field name="sentence">For example,machine-level virtualization will face challenges achieving high density, whilegVisor may provide poor performance for system call heavy workloads.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6242</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Why Go?</field><field name="sentence">gVisor was written in Go in order to avoid security pitfalls that can plaguekernels</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6243</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Why Go?</field><field name="sentence">With Go, there are strong types, built-in bounds checks, nouninitialized variables, no use-after-free, no stack overflow, and a built-inrace detector</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6244</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Why Go?</field><field name="sentence">The use of Go has its challenges too, and isn't free</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6245</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Architecture</field><field name="sentence">gVisor intercepts all system calls made by the application, and does thenecessary work to service them</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6246</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Architecture</field><field name="sentence">Importantly, gVisor does not simply redirectapplication system calls through to the host kernel</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6247</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Architecture</field><field name="sentence">Instead, gVisor implementsmost kernel primitives  signals, file systems, futexes, pipes, mm, etc</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6248</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Architecture</field><field name="sentence">and hascomplete system call handlers built on top of these primitives.Since gVisor is itself a user-space application, it will make some host systemcalls to support its operation, but much like a VMM, it will not allow theapplication to directly control the system calls it makes.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6249</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">File System Access</field><field name="sentence">In order to provide defense-in-depth and limit the host system surface, thegVisor container runtime is normally split into two separate processes</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6250</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">File System Access</field><field name="sentence">First,the *Sentrycode and handling system calls</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6251</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">File System Access</field><field name="sentence">Second, file system operations that extendbeyond the sandbox  not internal proc or tmp files, pipes, etc</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6252</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">File System Access</field><field name="sentence">are sent to aproxy, called a *Gofer*, via a 9P connection.! Sentry  g3doc/Sentry-Gofer.png "Sentry and Gofer" The Gofer acts as a file system proxy by opening host files on behalf of theapplication, and passing them to the Sentry process, which has no host fileaccess itself</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6253</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">File System Access</field><field name="sentence">Furthermore, the Sentry runs in an empty user namespace, and thesystem calls made by gVisor to the host are restricted using seccomp filters inorder to provide defense-in-depth.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6254</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Network Access</field><field name="sentence">The Sentry implements its own network stack  also written in Go  called netstack  netstack</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6255</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Network Access</field><field name="sentence">All aspects of the network stack are handled inside theSentry — including TCP connection state, control messages, and packet assembly —keeping it isolated from the host network stack</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6256</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Network Access</field><field name="sentence">Data link layer packets arewritten directly to the virtual device inside the network namespace setup byDocker or Kubernetes.A network passthrough mode is also supported, but comes at the cost of reducedisolation  see below .</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6257</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Platforms</field><field name="sentence">The Sentry requires a *platformmapping functionality</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6258</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Platforms</field><field name="sentence">Today, gVisor supports two platforms:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6259</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Performance</field><field name="sentence">There are several factors influencing performance</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6260</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Performance</field><field name="sentence">The platform choice has thelargest direct impact that varies depending on the specific workload</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6261</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Performance</field><field name="sentence">There isno best platform: Ptrace works universally, including on VM instances, butapplications may perform at a fraction of their original levels</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6262</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Performance</field><field name="sentence">Beyond theplatform choice, passthrough modes may be useful for improving perfomance at thecost of some isolation.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6263</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Installation</field><field name="sentence">These instructions will get you up-and-running sandboxed containers with gVisorand Docker.Note that gVisor can only run on x86\_64 Linux 3.17+</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6264</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Installation</field><field name="sentence">In addition, gVisor onlysupports x86\_64 binaries inside the sandbox  i.e., it cannot run 32-bitbinaries .</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6265</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Download a Build</field><field name="sentence">The easiest way to get {yyyy-mm-dd}/runsc.sha512**It is important to copy this binary to some place that is accessible to allusers**, since runsc executes itself as user nobody to avoid unnecessaryprivileges</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6266</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Download a Build</field><field name="sentence">The /usr/local/bin directory is a good choice.Next, configure Docker to use runsc by adding a runtime entry to your Dockerconfiguration  /etc/docker/daemon.json</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6267</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Download a Build</field><field name="sentence">You may have to create this file ifit does not exist</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6268</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Download a Build</field><field name="sentence">Also, some Docker versions also require you to specify the storage-driver field  docker-storage-driver .In the end, the file should look something like:this is done via:gVisor can run sandboxed containers in a Kubernetes cluster with cri-o, althoughthis is not recommended for production environments yet</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6269</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Download a Build</field><field name="sentence">Follow these instructions  cri-o-k8s  to run  cri-o  cri-o  on a node in a Kubernetescluster</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6270</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Download a Build</field><field name="sentence">Build runtime_untrusted_workload in /etc/crio/crio.conf.Any Pod without the io.kubernetes.cri-o.TrustedSandbox annotation  or with theannotation set to false  will be run with runsc.Currently, gVisor only supports Pods with a single container  not counting theever-present pause container</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6271</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Download a Build</field><field name="sentence">Support for multiple containers within a singlePod is coming soon.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6272</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Installing from Source</field><field name="sentence">gVisor currently requires x86\_64 Linux to build.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6273</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Requirements</field><field name="sentence">Make sure the following dependencies are installed:Clone the gVisor repo:Build and install the runsc binary.The gVisor test suite can be run with Bazel:To enable debug and system call logging, add the runtimeArgs below to yourDocker configuration  /etc/docker/daemon.json :restart the Docker daemon:with name boot will contain the strace logs from your application, which canbe useful for identifying missing or broken system calls in gVisor.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6274</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Enabling network passthrough</field><field name="sentence">For high-performance networking applications, you may choose to disable the userspace network stack and instead use the host network stack</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6275</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Enabling network passthrough</field><field name="sentence">Note that this modedecreases the isolation to the host.Add the following runtimeArgs to your Docker configuration /etc/docker/daemon.json  and restart the Docker daemon:Depending on hardware and performance characteristics, you may choose to use adifferent platform</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6276</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Enabling network passthrough</field><field name="sentence">The Ptrace platform is the default, but the KVM platform maybe specified by passing the --platform flag to runsc in your Dockerconfiguration  /etc/docker/daemon.json :</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6277</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Checkpoint/Restore</field><field name="sentence">gVisor has the ability to checkpoint a process, save its current state in astate file, and restore into a new container using the state file</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6278</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Checkpoint/Restore</field><field name="sentence">For moreinformation about the checkpoint and restore commands, see the checkpoint/restore readme  checkpoint-restore .</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6279</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Will my container work with gVisor?</field><field name="sentence">gVisor implements a large portion of the Linux surface and while we strive tomake it broadly compatible, there are  and always will be  unimplementedfeatures and bugs</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6280</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Will my container work with gVisor?</field><field name="sentence">The only real way to know if it will work is to try</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6281</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Will my container work with gVisor?</field><field name="sentence">If youfind a container that doesn’t work and there is no known issue, please file a bug  bug  indicating the full command you used to run the image.Providing the debug logs is also helpful.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6282</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">What works?</field><field name="sentence">The following applications/images have been tested:The following applications have been tested and may not yet work:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6283</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">My container runs fine with *runc</field><field name="sentence">If you’re having problems running a container with runsc it’s most likely dueto a compatibility issue or a missing feature in gVisor</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6284</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">My container runs fine with *runc</field><field name="sentence">See **Debugging**,</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6285</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">When I run my container, docker fails with flag provided but not defined: -console</field><field name="sentence">You're using an old version of Docker</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6286</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">When I run my container, docker fails with flag provided but not defined: -console</field><field name="sentence">Refer to the Requirements  #requirements  section for the minimum version supported.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6287</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">I can’t see a file copied with docker cp or kubectl cp.</field><field name="sentence">For performance reasons, gVisor caches directory contents, and therefore it maynot realize a new file was copied to a given directory</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6288</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">I can’t see a file copied with docker cp or kubectl cp.</field><field name="sentence">To invalidate the cacheand force a refresh, create a file under the directory in question and list thecontents again.This bug is tracked in  bug #4</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6289</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Technical details</field><field name="sentence">We plan to release a full paper with technical details and will include it herewhen available.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6290</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Community</field><field name="sentence">Join the  gvisor-users mailing list  gvisor-users-list  to discuss all thingsSensitive security-related questions and comments can be sent to the private gvisor-security mailing list  gvisor-security-list .</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6291</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Contributing</field><field name="sentence">See  Contributing.md  CONTRIBUTING.md</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6292</field><field name="title">google-gvisor</field><field name="session">Contributing</field><field name="sentence">apparmor :  bazel :  bug :  checkpoint-restore :  cri-o-k8s :  cri-o :  docker-storage-driver :  docker :  git :  gvisor-security-list :  gvisor-users-list :  kvm :  netstack :  oci :  python :  runsc-nightly-sha :  runsc-nightly :  sandbox :  seccomp :  selinux :  uml :  xen :</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6293</field><field name="title">google-gwteventbinder</field><field name="session">What is EventBinder?</field><field name="sentence">GWT's EventBus is great by decoupling the components of your application, making them easy to add,modify, or remove</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6294</field><field name="title">google-gwteventbinder</field><field name="session">What is EventBinder?</field><field name="sentence">However, using EventBus in GWT can require a lot of boilerplate in the form of implementing events, defining handler interfaces forthem, and implementing those interfaces all over your code in anonymous classes.EventBinder automates away these boring details using a strategy similar to the@UiHandler annotation defined by UiBinder.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6295</field><field name="title">google-gwteventbinder</field><field name="session">How do I use it?</field><field name="sentence">Easy</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6296</field><field name="title">google-gwteventbinder</field><field name="session">Defining events</field><field name="sentence">With EventBinder, events are just immutable value types extending GenericEvent</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6297</field><field name="title">google-gwteventbinder</field><field name="session">Defining events</field><field name="sentence">If your event doesn't have any arguments, defining itonly takes one line:public class EmailLoadedEvent extends GenericEvent {  private final String subject;  private final String body;  }  public String getBody   { return body; }That's it GwtEvent or to define handler interfaces.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6298</field><field name="title">google-gwteventbinder</field><field name="session">Registering event handlers</field><field name="sentence">Event handlers are methods annotated with the UiBinder</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6299</field><field name="title">google-gwteventbinder</field><field name="session">Registering event handlers</field><field name="sentence">Here's an example:class EmailPresenter {  interface MyEventBinder extends EventBinder {}  private final MyEventBinder eventBinder = GWT.create MyEventBinder.class ;  }  void onEmailLoaded EmailLoadedEvent event  {  }After EmailLoadedEvent is fired on the given event bus.It's possible to handle several events in one method</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6300</field><field name="title">google-gwteventbinder</field><field name="session">Registering event handlers</field><field name="sentence">In this case you mustenumerate these event classes in handles is specified and you don't need event parameter you may omit it.class SuperEvent extends GenericEvent { }class EventOne extends SuperEvent { }class EventTwo extends SuperEvent { }class FormPresenter {  interface MyEventBinder extends EventBinder {}  private final MyEventBinder eventBinder = GWT.create MyEventBinder.class ;  }  void onEventOne EventOne event  {  }  void onEventOneAndTwo SuperEvent event  {  }  void onEventOneAndTwo2   {  }</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6301</field><field name="title">google-gwteventbinder</field><field name="session">Firing events</field><field name="sentence">The last step is easy and doesn't require anything special from EventBinderapplication to be invoked in an undefined order</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6302</field><field name="title">google-gwteventbinder</field><field name="session">Firing events</field><field name="sentence">That's it, you're done!</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6303</field><field name="title">google-gwteventbinder</field><field name="session">How do I install it?</field><field name="sentence">If you're using Maven, you can add the following to your from and build it yourself</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6304</field><field name="title">google-gwteventbinder</field><field name="session">How do I install it?</field><field name="sentence">Onceyou've installed EventBinder, be sure to inherit the module in your .gwt.xmlfile like this:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6305</field><field name="title">google-gwteventbinder</field><field name="session">1.1.0</field><field name="sentence">1 :  2 :  3 :  4 :  5 :</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6306</field><field name="title">google-gwtmockito</field><field name="session">What is GwtMockito?</field><field name="sentence">Testing GWT applications using GWTTestCase can be a pain using pure Java tests, and you can't use reflection-based tools like mockingframeworks</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6307</field><field name="title">google-gwtmockito</field><field name="session">What is GwtMockito?</field><field name="sentence">But if you've tried to test widgets using normal test cases, you'veprobably run into this error:GwtMockito solves this and other GWT-related testing problems by allowing youto call GWT.create from JUnit tests, returning  Mockito  1  mocks.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6308</field><field name="title">google-gwtmockito</field><field name="session">How do I use it?</field><field name="sentence">Getting started with GwtMockito using Junit 4.5+ is easy</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6309</field><field name="title">google-gwtmockito</field><field name="session">How do I use it?</field><field name="sentence">Just annotate your testwith @RunWith GwtMockitoTestRunner.class , then any calls to GWT.createencountered will return Mockito mocks instead of throwing exceptions:populate @UiFields with Mockito mocks</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6310</field><field name="title">google-gwtmockito</field><field name="session">How do I use it?</field><field name="sentence">Suppose you have a widget that lookslike this:public class MyWidget extends Composite {  interface MyUiBinder extends UiBinder {}  private final MyUiBinder uiBinder = GWT.create MyUiBinder.class ;  private final NumberFormatter formatter;  }  }When numberLabel with a mock object</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6311</field><field name="title">google-gwtmockito</field><field name="session">How do I use it?</field><field name="sentence">Since @UiFields are package-visible, they can be read from your unit tests, which lets you test this widget as follows:@RunWith GwtMockitoTestRunner.class public class MyWidgetTest {  private MyWidget widget;  public void setUp   {  }  public void shouldFormatNumber   {  }Note that GwtMockito supports the @Mock annotation from Mockito, allowing standard Mockito mocks to be mixed with mocks created by GwtMockito.That's all you need to know to get started hearing about some advanced features.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6312</field><field name="title">google-gwtmockito</field><field name="session">Accessing the mock returned from GWT.create</field><field name="sentence">Returning mocks from GWT.create isn't very useful if you don't have any way toverify or set behaviors on them</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6313</field><field name="title">google-gwtmockito</field><field name="session">Accessing the mock returned from GWT.create</field><field name="sentence">You can do this by annotating a field in your test with @GwtMock to return a mock stored in that field, allowing you to reference it in yourtest</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6314</field><field name="title">google-gwtmockito</field><field name="session">Accessing the mock returned from GWT.create</field><field name="sentence">So if you have a class that looks like@RunWith GwtMockitoTestRunner.class public class MyClassTest {  @GwtMock SomeInterface mockInterface;  public void constructorShouldSetSomething   {  }</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6315</field><field name="title">google-gwtmockito</field><field name="session">Returning fake objects</field><field name="sentence">By default, GwtMockito will return fake implementations  which don't require youto specify mock behavior  for any classes extending the following types:GwtMockito.useProviderForType Class, FakeProvider  in your setUp method</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6316</field><field name="title">google-gwtmockito</field><field name="session">Returning fake objects</field><field name="sentence">This will cause all calls to GWT.create for the given class or its subclassesto invoke the given FakeProvider to determine what to return</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6317</field><field name="title">google-gwtmockito</field><field name="session">Returning fake objects</field><field name="sentence">See the javadoc reference  2  for more details.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6318</field><field name="title">google-gwtmockito</field><field name="session">Mocking final classes and methods</field><field name="sentence">Mockito does not normally allow final classes and methods to be mocked</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6319</field><field name="title">google-gwtmockito</field><field name="session">Mocking final classes and methods</field><field name="sentence">This poses problems in GWT since  JavaScript overlay types  3   which include Element and its subclasses  require all methods to be final</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6320</field><field name="title">google-gwtmockito</field><field name="session">Mocking final classes and methods</field><field name="sentence">Fortunately,GwtMockito does some classloader black magic to remove all final modifiers fromclasses and interfaces, so the following test will pass:@RunWith GwtMockitoTestRunner.class public class MyTest {  @Mock Element element;  public void shouldReturnMocksFromGwtCreate   {  }As long as your test uses GwtMockitoTestRunner, it is possible to mock anyfinal methods.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6321</field><field name="title">google-gwtmockito</field><field name="session">Dealing with native methods</field><field name="sentence">Under normal circumstances, JUnit tests will fail with an UnsatisfiedLinkError when encountering a native JSNI method</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6322</field><field name="title">google-gwtmockito</field><field name="session">Dealing with native methods</field><field name="sentence">GwtMockito works around this problemusing more classloader black magic to provide no-op implementations for allnative methods using the following rules:These rules allow many tests to continue to work even when calling incindentalnative methods</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6323</field><field name="title">google-gwtmockito</field><field name="session">Dealing with native methods</field><field name="sentence">Note that this can be dangerous always returns GWTTestCase.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6324</field><field name="title">google-gwtmockito</field><field name="session">Support for JUnit 3 and other tests that can't use custom runners</field><field name="sentence">Though GwtMockito.initMocks directly</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6325</field><field name="title">google-gwtmockito</field><field name="session">Support for JUnit 3 and other tests that can't use custom runners</field><field name="sentence">A test written in this style looks like this:public class MyWidgetTest extends TestCase {  public void setUp   {  }  public void tearDown   {  }  }The test must explicitly call initMocks during its setup and tearDown whenit is being teared down, or else state can leak between tests</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6326</field><field name="title">google-gwtmockito</field><field name="session">Support for JUnit 3 and other tests that can't use custom runners</field><field name="sentence">When instantiating a widget, the test must also subclass it and override initWidgetwith a no-op implementation, or else it will fail when this method attempts tocall Javascript</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6327</field><field name="title">google-gwtmockito</field><field name="session">Support for JUnit 3 and other tests that can't use custom runners</field><field name="sentence">Note that when testing in this way the features described in"Mocking final classes and methods" and "Dealing with native methods" won'twork methods without using GwtMockitoTestRunner.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6328</field><field name="title">google-gwtmockito</field><field name="session">How do I install it?</field><field name="sentence">If you're using Maven, you can add the following to your from <></field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6329</field><field name="title">google-gwtmockito</field><field name="session">How do I install it?</field><field name="sentence">In these cases you will haveto manually install the jars for  Mockito  6  and  Javassist  7 .</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6330</field><field name="title">google-gwtmockito</field><field name="session">1.0.0</field><field name="sentence">2 :  3 :  4 :  5 :  6 :  7 :  8 :  9 :  10 :</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6331</field><field name="title">google-gxui</field><field name="session">Linux:</field><field name="sentence">In order to build GXUI on linux, you will need the following packages installed:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6332</field><field name="title">google-gxui</field><field name="session">Common:</field><field name="sentence">After setting up GOPATH  see  Go documentation  you can then fetch the GXUI library and its dependencies:--To build all samples run:And they will be built into GOPATH/bin.If you add GOPATH/bin to your PATH, you can simply type the name of a sample to run it</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6333</field><field name="title">google-gxui</field><field name="session">Common:</field><field name="sentence">For example: image_viewer.---gxui code is cross platform and can be compiled using GopherJS to JavaScript, allowing it to run in browsers with WebGL support</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6334</field><field name="title">google-gxui</field><field name="session">Common:</field><field name="sentence">To do so, you'll need the  GopherJS compiler  and some additional dependencies:--This is built into the gxfont package.Make sure to mention this font in any notices file distributed with your application.--Contributions, however small, will require the author to have signed the  Google Individual Contributor License Agreement The CLA is necessary mainly because you own the copyright to your changes, even after your contribution becomes part of our codebase, so we need your permission to use and distribute your code</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6335</field><field name="title">google-gxui</field><field name="session">Common:</field><field name="sentence">We also need to be sure of various other things—for instance that you'll tell us if you know that your code infringes on other people's patents</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6336</field><field name="title">google-gxui</field><field name="session">Common:</field><field name="sentence">You don't have to sign the CLA until after you've submitted your code for review and a member has approved it, but you must do it before we can put your code into our codebase</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6337</field><field name="title">google-gxui</field><field name="session">Common:</field><field name="sentence">Before you start working on a larger contribution, you should get in touch with us first through the issue tracker with your idea so that we can help out and possibly guide you</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6338</field><field name="title">google-gxui</field><field name="session">Common:</field><field name="sentence">Coordinating up front makes it much easier to avoid frustration later on.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6339</field><field name="title">google-har-sanitizer</field><field name="session">Description</field><field name="sentence">HAR files are JSON-formatted "recordings" of web traffic activity for a user's browser session, which are often used to troubleshoot web front-ends, REST APIs, authentication issues, etc</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6340</field><field name="title">google-har-sanitizer</field><field name="session">Description</field><field name="sentence">However, HAR files will capture everything in a web session, including passwords, sensitive form information, authentication cookies and headers, and any content embedded in HTTP requests</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6341</field><field name="title">google-har-sanitizer</field><field name="session">Description</field><field name="sentence">This makes HAR files extremely sensitive, and highly prone to privacy breaches if handled incorrectly.This tool aims to help mitigate these concerns by offering a simple, flexible interface to redact HAR file contents of any potentially sensitive information</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6342</field><field name="title">google-har-sanitizer</field><field name="session">Description</field><field name="sentence">It collects the names and values of all passwords, cookies, headers, URLQuery/POSTData/HTML-Form parameters, and embedded content mimetypes, and redacts values either already known to be sensitive, or those specified by the user</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6343</field><field name="title">google-har-sanitizer</field><field name="session">Description</field><field name="sentence">It currently exists as a both a client-side web tool and Flask REST API.Live version may be found at  This is NOT an official Google product</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6344</field><field name="title">google-har-sanitizer</field><field name="session">Installation</field><field name="sentence">If virtual environment not already activated If desired, change static files location in config.json</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6345</field><field name="title">google-har-sanitizer</field><field name="session">Installation</field><field name="sentence">Examples:{  "static_files": "./harsanitizer/static"  "static_files": ""Change port, debug, and other options in ./harsanitizer/harsan_api.py under:Launch Flask server:Load the Har-Sanitizer web tool by visiting "" in Chrome or Firefox  substituting '8080' with the port #, if modified .</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6346</field><field name="title">google-har-sanitizer</field><field name="session">Web Tool</field><field name="sentence">Load HAR JSON file using 'Load HAR' button.Select names of cookies/headers/parameters/content mimetypes to scrub.Preview changes before committing, modifying scrub options as necessary.Export scrubbed HAR file once ready.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6347</field><field name="title">google-har-sanitizer</field><field name="session">API Endpoint</field><field name="sentence">import json, requests  with open "har_file.har", "r"  as har_file:  url = '  headers = {"Content-Type": "application/json"}  r = requests.post url, data=json.dumps har , headers=headers</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6348</field><field name="title">google-har-sanitizer</field><field name="session">TODO</field><field name="sentence">Needs tests bad</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6349</field><field name="title">google-har-sanitizer</field><field name="session">TODO</field><field name="sentence">This should be current priority</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6350</field><field name="title">google-har-sanitizer</field><field name="session">TODO</field><field name="sentence">Use pytest and Jasmine.Other issues are being tracked in Github  issue tracker</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6351</field><field name="title">google-har-sanitizer</field><field name="session">Contact</field><field name="sentence">Garrett Anderson:Geoffrey Coulter:Copyright 2017, Google Inc.Authors: Garrett AndersonLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0  the "License" ;you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.You may obtain a copy of the License atUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, softwaredistributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.See the License for the specific language governing permissions andlimitations under the License</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6352</field><field name="title">google-hashing-demo</field><field name="session">#Introduction</field><field name="sentence">This is a sample implementation of a forthcoming C++ standard libraryproposal</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6353</field><field name="title">google-hashing-demo</field><field name="session">#Introduction</field><field name="sentence">It is intended only for demonstration and evaluation purposes,and is not suitable for use in production systems</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6354</field><field name="title">google-hashing-demo</field><field name="session">#Introduction</field><field name="sentence">This is not an officialGoogle product  experimental or otherwise , it is just code that happensto be owned by Google.The APIs in  std.h  std.h  and  std_impl.h  std_impl.h  are proposed forstandardization</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6355</field><field name="title">google-hashing-demo</field><field name="session">#Introduction</field><field name="sentence">fnv1a.h  fnv1a.h  and  farmhash.h  farmhash.h  are exampleimplementations of particular algorithms using this framework, but are notthemselves proposed for standardization</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6356</field><field name="title">google-hashing-demo</field><field name="session">#Introduction</field><field name="sentence">std_test.cc  std_test.cc  shows somesimple examples of the extension API for type owners, as well as the end-userAPI  which is just std::hash .The code uses some C++14 language and library features</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6357</field><field name="title">google-hashing-demo</field><field name="session">#Introduction</field><field name="sentence">It doesn't work withlibstdc++ as of version 4.8, but it does work with libc++ 3.A CMakeLists.txt  CMakeLists.txt  is included for building the tests with CMake  Example usage:-DCMAKE_INCLUDE_PATH, respectively</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6358</field><field name="title">google-hashing-demo</field><field name="session">#Introduction</field><field name="sentence">Similarly, the benchmarks depend on google/benchmark  This is includedas a git submodule  run git submodule init; git submodule update to setit up , or you can install the source distribution in another location,and configure that location with -Dbenchmark_src_dir.API documentation will be provided in the forthcoming paper.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6359</field><field name="title">google-hashtable-benchmarks</field><field name="session">Hashtable Benchmarks</field><field name="sentence">Benchmarks for comparing hashtable implementations.You can use  along with hashtable_benchmarks.ipynb to parse the generated benchmark-results.json.We would like this to turn into *thewill accept external dependencies on other hashtable libraries  assuming theyhave a compatible licence</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6360</field><field name="title">google-hashtable-benchmarks</field><field name="session">Hashtable Benchmarks</field><field name="sentence">We encourage folks to improve and modify both theanalysis and the benchmarks themselves as we learn things</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6361</field><field name="title">google-hashtable-benchmarks</field><field name="session">Hashtable Benchmarks</field><field name="sentence">Please join thedicussion atThis is not an officially supported Google product.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6362</field><field name="title">google-haskell-indexer</field><field name="session">Supported systems</field><field name="sentence">Indexing hosts:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6363</field><field name="title">google-haskell-indexer</field><field name="session">Stack</field><field name="sentence">Download Stack from</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6364</field><field name="title">google-haskell-indexer</field><field name="session">Kythe</field><field name="sentence">If you want to use the Kythe frontend, download a  Kytherelease  and unpack it.If you want to install Kythe in a different location to /opt/kythe then youshould also set KYTHE_DIR to the location of the installation.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6365</field><field name="title">google-haskell-indexer</field><field name="session">Protoc 3</field><field name="sentence">Download the latest  Proto compiler 3release  unpack it and place thebinary in the PATH.> this.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6366</field><field name="title">google-haskell-indexer</field><field name="session">Build the project</field><field name="sentence">Use the following to build and run tests:To index a few packages, run:To serve the index at :possible indexing errors</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6367</field><field name="title">google-haskell-indexer</field><field name="session">Build the project</field><field name="sentence">Also, make sure that the *.entries files are notempty</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6368</field><field name="title">google-haskell-indexer</field><field name="session">Build the project</field><field name="sentence">If they are, it indicates that ghc_kythe_wrapper failed to index.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6369</field><field name="title">google-haskell-indexer</field><field name="session">Indexing using Docker</field><field name="sentence">If you plan to use the Dockerized build feature of stack, please installDocker</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6370</field><field name="title">google-haskell-indexer</field><field name="session">Indexing using Docker</field><field name="sentence">It is also advised to set up a docker wrapper script by following theinstructions at the  stack Dockersecurity The docker image has all C library dependencies so it's possible to use it toindex the whole Stackage snapshot</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6371</field><field name="title">google-haskell-indexer</field><field name="session">Indexing using Docker</field><field name="sentence">See stack-build-docker.sh for acomprehensive example of indexing a Stackage snapshot, and serving a Kythe</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6372</field><field name="title">google-hdrnet</field><field name="session">Deep Bilateral Learning for Real-Time Image Enhancements</field><field name="sentence">Siggraph 2017Visit our  Project Page  Michael Gharbi Jiawen ChenJonathan T</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6373</field><field name="title">google-hdrnet</field><field name="session">Deep Bilateral Learning for Real-Time Image Enhancements</field><field name="sentence">BarronSamuel W</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6374</field><field name="title">google-hdrnet</field><field name="session">Deep Bilateral Learning for Real-Time Image Enhancements</field><field name="sentence">HasinoffFredo DurandMaintained by Michael Gharbi   Tested on Python 2.7, Ubuntu 14.0, gcc-4.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6375</field><field name="title">google-hdrnet</field><field name="session">Disclaimer</field><field name="sentence">This is not an official Google product.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6376</field><field name="title">google-hdrnet</field><field name="session">Dependencies</field><field name="sentence">To install the Python dependencies, run:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6377</field><field name="title">google-hdrnet</field><field name="session">Build</field><field name="sentence">Our network requires a custom Tensorflow operator to "slice" in the bilateral grid.To build it, run:To build the benchmarking code, run:Note that the benchmarking code requires a frozen and optimized model</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6378</field><field name="title">google-hdrnet</field><field name="session">Build</field><field name="sentence">Usehdrnet/bin/scripts/optimize_graph.sh and hdrnet/bin/freeze.py to produce these.To build the Android demo, see dedicated section below.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6379</field><field name="title">google-hdrnet</field><field name="session">Test</field><field name="sentence">Run the test suite to make sure the BilateralSlice operator works correctly:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6380</field><field name="title">google-hdrnet</field><field name="session">Download pretrained models</field><field name="sentence">We provide a set of pretrained models</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6381</field><field name="title">google-hdrnet</field><field name="session">Download pretrained models</field><field name="sentence">One of these is included in the repo see pretrained_models/local_laplacian_sample</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6382</field><field name="title">google-hdrnet</field><field name="session">Download pretrained models</field><field name="sentence">To download the rest of them</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6383</field><field name="title">google-hdrnet</field><field name="session">Usage</field><field name="sentence">To train a model, run the following command:Look at sample_data/identity/ for a typical structure of the training data folder.You can monitor the training process using Tensorboard:To run a trained model on a novel image  or set of images , use:To prepare a model for use on mobile, freeze the graph, and optimize the network:You will need to change the ${TF_BASE} environment variable in ./hdrnet/bin/scripts/optimize_graph.shand compile the necessary tensorflow command line tools for this  automated in the script .</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6384</field><field name="title">google-hdrnet</field><field name="session">Android prototype</field><field name="sentence">We will add it to this repo soon.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6385</field><field name="title">google-hdrnet</field><field name="session">Known issues and limitations</field><field name="sentence">Apply white balance channel gains</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6386</field><field name="title">google-hdrnet</field><field name="session">Known issues and limitations</field><field name="sentence">Demosaic to RGB</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6387</field><field name="title">google-hdrnet</field><field name="session">Known issues and limitations</field><field name="sentence">Apply lens shading correction  aka vignetting correction</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6388</field><field name="title">google-hdrnet</field><field name="session">Known issues and limitations</field><field name="sentence">white balance, and tone mapping performed by the Qualcomm SOC</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6389</field><field name="title">google-hdrnet</field><field name="session">Known issues and limitations</field><field name="sentence">It results in slightly different colors than that on the test set</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6390</field><field name="title">google-hdrnet</field><field name="session">Known issues and limitations</field><field name="sentence">If you run our HDR+ model on an sRGB input, it may produce uncanny colors.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6391</field><field name="title">google-hell0world-curriculum</field><field name="session">hell0world Curriculum</field><field name="sentence">This is the open source curriculum for hell0world.org classes that are taught at Heart of Los Angeles  and can also be pursued on aself-paced basis.This is not an officially supported Google product.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6392</field><field name="title">google-hell0world-curriculum</field><field name="session">Projects</field><field name="sentence">If you're interested in contributing to the project, please check outCONTRIBUTING.md for guidelines.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6393</field><field name="title">google-helloargdx</field><field name="session">Hello AR GDX</field><field name="sentence">This is a port of the hello ar sample for ARCore to libGDX.The most obvious advantage to this implemention is that thereis no requirement to use or understand OpenGL ES, which isa large barrier to creating augmented reality apps in Java.The sample shows the basics of ARCore: plane detection, anchoring objectsin space, and light estimation  coming soon</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6394</field><field name="title">google-helloargdx</field><field name="session">Hello AR GDX</field><field name="sentence">In addition, it illustrateshow to use GDX to make an application and integrate non-graphical AndroidUI such as Snackbars into the activity.This is not an official Google product.I work at Google, but this specific project was created personallyas I investigated using ARCore in Java apps</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6395</field><field name="title">google-helloargdx</field><field name="session">Hello AR GDX</field><field name="sentence">I can't commit to maintainingor supporting this project's use.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6396</field><field name="title">google-helloargdx</field><field name="session">LICENSE</field><field name="sentence">Copyright 2017 Google Inc.Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0  the "License" ;you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.You may obtain a copy of the License at</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6397</field><field name="title">google-helm-broker</field><field name="session">Service Broker</field><field name="sentence">This is an implementation of a service broker which runs in a Kubernetescluster and deploys Kubernetes native resources only using Helm as the reifier.This is not an official Google product.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6398</field><field name="title">google-helm-broker</field><field name="session">Prerequisites</field><field name="sentence">1  A  helm  tiller running in the cluster.2   Glide  installed and in your path.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6399</field><field name="title">google-helm-broker</field><field name="session">Building and deploying</field><field name="sentence">To install the dependencies, build the binaries, run the tests, and build the Dockerimages, run the following:where ${PROJECT_NAME} is the name of your GCP project:curl -X POST -d @  "name": "nginx",  "id": "4179E70A-4641-49D5-B395-A8ACB1419BCA",  "description": "Helm chart for running nginx",  "plans":     ,  "requires":   ,  "tags":   ,  "bindable":false__EOF__</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6400</field><field name="title">google-helm-broker</field><field name="session">Create an instance of it</field><field name="sentence">curl -X PUT -d @  "service_id": "4179E70A-4641-49D5-B395-A8ACB1419BCA",  "plan_id":"696AD474-123F-474F-8FDB-C724C058CF03"__EOF__</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6401</field><field name="title">google-heroku-buildpack-bazel</field><field name="session">heroku-buildpack-bazel</field><field name="sentence">Heroku buildpack for  Bazel  Currenly, only Java is supported.Bazel is an open-source build tool created by and for the engineers at Google.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6402</field><field name="title">google-heroku-buildpack-bazel</field><field name="session">Default Procfile</field><field name="sentence">The default This does not need to be included in your app.If you need custom JVM flags, you'll need to include a custom Procfile with your application</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6403</field><field name="title">google-heroku-buildpack-bazel</field><field name="session">Default Procfile</field><field name="sentence">Modify the line above with the flags you want.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6404</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Quick Start</field><field name="sentence">To build on a Linux or Mac platform, simply run make</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6405</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Quick Start</field><field name="sentence">For Windows, we providea Visual Studio 2015 project in the msvc subdirectory.Run benchmark for speed measurements</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6406</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Quick Start</field><field name="sentence">sip_hash_test and highwayhash_testensure the implementations return known-good values for a given set of inputs.64-bit SipHash for any CPU:64, 128 or 256 bit HighwayHash for the CPU determined by compiler flags:64, 128 or 256 bit HighwayHash for the CPU on which we're currently running:C-callable 64-bit HighwayHash for the CPU on which we're currently running:Printing a 256-bit result in a hexadecimal format similar to sha1sum:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6407</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Introduction</field><field name="sentence">Hash functions are widely used, so it is desirable to increase their speed andsecurity</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6408</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Introduction</field><field name="sentence">This package provides two 'strong'  well-distributed andunpredictable  hash functions: a faster version of SipHash, and an even fasteralgorithm we call HighwayHash.SipHash is a fast but 'cryptographically strong' pseudo-random function byAumasson and Bernstein   .HighwayHash is a new way of mixing inputs which may inspire newcryptographically strong hashes</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6409</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Introduction</field><field name="sentence">Large inputs are processed at a rate of 0.24cycles per byte, and latency remains low even for small inputs</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6410</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Introduction</field><field name="sentence">HighwayHash isfaster than SipHash for all input sizes, with 5 times higher throughput at 1KiB</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6411</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Introduction</field><field name="sentence">We discuss design choices and provide statistical analysis and preliminarycryptanalysis in</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6412</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Applications</field><field name="sentence">Unlike prior strong hashes, these functions are fast enough to be recommendedas safer replacements for weak hashes in many applications</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6413</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Applications</field><field name="sentence">The additional CPUcost appears affordable, based on profiling data indicating C++ hash functionsaccount for less than 0.25% of CPU usage.Hash-based selection of random subsets is useful for A/B experiments and similarapplications</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6414</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Applications</field><field name="sentence">Such random generators are idempotent  repeatable anddeterministic , which is helpful for parallel algorithms and testing</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6415</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Applications</field><field name="sentence">To avoidbias, it is important that the hash function be unpredictable andindistinguishable from a uniform random generator</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6416</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Applications</field><field name="sentence">We have verified the bitdistribution and avalanche properties of SipHash and HighwayHash.64-bit hashes are also useful for authenticating short-lived messages such asnetwork/RPC packets</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6417</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Applications</field><field name="sentence">This requires that the hash function withstanddifferential, length extension and other attacks</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6418</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Applications</field><field name="sentence">We have published a formalsecurity analysis for HighwayHash</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6419</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Applications</field><field name="sentence">New cryptanalysis tools may still need to bedeveloped for further analysis.Strong hashes are also important parts of methods for protecting hash tablesagainst unacceptable worst-case behavior and denial of service attacks see "hash flooding" below .128 and 256-bit hashes can be useful for verifying data integrity  checksums .</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6420</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">SipHash</field><field name="sentence">Our SipHash implementation is a fast and portable drop-in replacement forthe reference C code</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6421</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">SipHash</field><field name="sentence">Outputs are identical for the given test cases  messagesbetween 0 and 63 bytes .Interestingly, it is about twice as fast as a SIMD implementation using SSE4.1 This is presumably due to the lack of SIMD bit rotateinstructions prior to AVX-SipHash13 is a faster but weaker variant with one mixing round per update andthree during finalization.We also provide a data-parallel 'tree hash' variant that enables efficient SIMDwhile retaining safety guarantees</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6422</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">SipHash</field><field name="sentence">This is about twice as fast as SipHash, butdoes not return the same results.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6423</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">HighwayHash</field><field name="sentence">We have devised a new way of mixing inputs with AVX2 multiply and permuteinstructions</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6424</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">HighwayHash</field><field name="sentence">The multiplications are 32x32 -> 64 bits and therefore infeasibleto reverse</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6425</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">HighwayHash</field><field name="sentence">Permuting equalizes the distribution of the resulting bytes.The internal state occupies four 256-bit AVX2 registers</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6426</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">HighwayHash</field><field name="sentence">Due to limitations ofthe instruction set, the registers are partitioned into two 512-bit halves thatremain independent until the reduce phase</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6427</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">HighwayHash</field><field name="sentence">The algorithm outputs 64 bit digestsor up to 256 bits at no extra cost.In addition to high throughput, the algorithm is designed for low finalizationcost</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6428</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">HighwayHash</field><field name="sentence">The result is more than twice as fast as SipTreeHash.We also provide an SSE4.1 version  80% as fast for large inputs and 95% as fastfor short inputs , an implementation for VSX on POWER and a portable version 10% as fast</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6429</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">HighwayHash</field><field name="sentence">A third-party ARM implementation is referenced below.Statistical analyses and preliminary cryptanalysis are given in</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6430</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Versioning and stability</field><field name="sentence">Now that 21 months have elapsed since their initial release, we have declaredall  64/128/256 bit  variants of HighwayHash frozen, i.e</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6431</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Versioning and stability</field><field name="sentence">unchanging forever.SipHash and HighwayHash are 'fingerprint functions' whose input -> hashmapping will not change</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6432</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Versioning and stability</field><field name="sentence">This is important for applications that write hashes topersistent storage.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6433</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Speed measurements</field><field name="sentence">To measure the CPU cost of a hash function, we can either create an artificial'microbenchmark'  easier to control, but probably not representative of theactual runtime , or insert instrumentation directly into an application  risksinfluencing the results through observer overhead</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6434</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Speed measurements</field><field name="sentence">We provide novel variants ofboth approaches that mitigate their respective disadvantages.profiler.h uses software write-combining to stream program traces to memorywith minimal overhead</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6435</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Speed measurements</field><field name="sentence">These can be analyzed offline, or when memory is full,to learn how much time was spent in each  possibly nested  zone.nanobenchmark.h enables cycle-accurate measurements of very short functions.It uses CPU fences and robust statistics to minimize variability, and alsoavoids unrealistic branch prediction effects.We compile the 64-bit C++ implementations with a patched GCC 4.9 and run on asingle idle core of a Xeon E5-2690 v3 clocked at 2.6 GHz</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6436</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Speed measurements</field><field name="sentence">CPU cost is measuredas cycles per byte for various input sizes:---------------HighwayHashAVX2  | 7.34  | 1.81 | 1.71 | 1.04 | 0.95 | 0.24HighwayHashSSE41 | 8.00  | 2.11 | 1.75 | 1.13 | 0.96 | 0.30SipTreeHash13SipHash13SipTreeHash is slower than SipHash for small inputs because it processes blocksof 32 bytes</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6437</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Speed measurements</field><field name="sentence">AVX2 and SSE4.1 HighwayHash are faster than SipHash for all inputsizes due to their highly optimized handling of partial vectors.Note that previous measurements included the initialization of their input,which dramatically increased timings especially for small inputs.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6438</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">CPU requirements</field><field name="sentence">SipTreeHash 13  requires an AVX2-capable CPU  e.g</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6439</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">CPU requirements</field><field name="sentence">Haswell</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6440</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">CPU requirements</field><field name="sentence">HighwayHashincludes a dispatcher that chooses the best available  AVX2, SSE4.1, VSX orportable  implementation at runtime, as well as a directly callable functiontemplate that can only run on the CPU for which it was built</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6441</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">CPU requirements</field><field name="sentence">SipHash 13  andScalarSipTreeHash 13  have no particular CPU requirements.Our x86 implementations use custom vector classes with overloaded operators e.g</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6442</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">CPU requirements</field><field name="sentence">const V4x64U a = b + c  for type-safety and improved readability vs.compiler intrinsics  e.g</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6443</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">CPU requirements</field><field name="sentence">const __m256i a = _mm256_add_epi64 b, c  .The VSX implementation uses built-in vector types alongside Altivec intrinsics.A high-performance third-party ARM implementation is mentioned below.Our instruction_sets dispatcher avoids running newer instructions on older CPUsthat do not support them</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6444</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">CPU requirements</field><field name="sentence">However, intrinsics, and therefore also any vectorclasses that use them, require a compiler flag that also enables the compiler togenerate code for that CPU</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6445</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">CPU requirements</field><field name="sentence">This means the intrinsics must be placed in separatetranslation units that are compiled with the required flags</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6446</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">CPU requirements</field><field name="sentence">It is importantthat these source files and their headers not define any inline functions,because that might break the one definition rule and cause crashes.To minimize dispatch overhead when hashes are computed often  e.g</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6447</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">CPU requirements</field><field name="sentence">in a loop ,we can inline the hash function into its caller using templates</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6448</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">CPU requirements</field><field name="sentence">The dispatchoverhead will only be paid once  e.g</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6449</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">CPU requirements</field><field name="sentence">before the loop</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6450</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">CPU requirements</field><field name="sentence">The template mechanismalso avoids duplicating code in each CPU-specific implementation.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6451</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">To mitigate hash flooding attacks, we need to take both the hash function andthe data structure into account.We wish to defend  web  services that utilize hash sets/maps againstdenial-of-service attacks</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6452</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">Such data structures assign attacker-controlledinput messages m to a hash table bin b by computing the hash H s, m using a hash function H seeded by s, and mapping it to a bin with somenarrowing function b = R h , discussed below.Attackers may attempt to trigger 'flooding'  excessive work in insertions orlookups  by finding multiple m that map to the same bin</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6453</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">If the attacker haslocal access, they can do far worse, so we assume the attacker can only issueremote requests</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6454</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">If the attacker is able to send large numbers of requests,they can already deny service, so we need only ensure the attacker's cost issufficiently large compared to the service's provisioning.If the hash function is 'weak', attackers can easily generate 'hash collisions' inputs mapping to the same hash values  that are independent of the seed</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6455</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">Inother words, certain input messages will cause collisions regardless of the seedvalue</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6456</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">The author of SipHash has published C++ programs to generate such'universal  key-independent  multicollisions' for CityHash and Murmur</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6457</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">Similar'differential' attacks are likely possible for any hash function consisting onlyof reversible operations  e.g</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6458</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">addition/multiplication/rotation  with a constantoperand</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6459</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">n requests with such inputs cause n^2 work for an unprotected hashtable, which is unacceptable.By contrast, 'strong' hashes such as SipHash or HighwayHash require infeasibleattacker effort to find a hash collision  an expected 2^32 guesses of m perthe birthday paradox  or recover the seed  2^63 requests</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6460</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">These security claimsassume the seed is secret</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6461</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">It is reasonable to suppose s is initially unknownto attackers, e.g</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6462</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">generated on startup or even per-connection</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6463</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">A timing attackby Wool/Bar-Yosef recovers 13-bit seeds by testing all 8K possibilities usingmillions of requests, which takes several days  even assuming unrealistic 150 usround-trip times</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6464</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">It appears infeasible to recover 64-bit seeds in this way.However, attackers are only looking for multiple R h  := h &  p easier for attackers to compute partial collisions where only the lower i bitsmatch</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6465</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">This can be prevented by choosing a prime p so that R h  := h % pincorporates all hash bits</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6466</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">The costly modulo operation can be avoided bymultiplying with the inverse  An interesting alternativesuggested by Kyoung Jae Seo chooses a random subset of the h bits</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6467</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">Such an Rfunction can be computed in just 3 cycles using PEXT from the BMI2 instructionset</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6468</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">This is expected to defend against SAT-solver attacks on the hash bits at aslightly lower cost than the multiplicative inverse method, and still allowspower-of-two table sizes.Summary thus far: given a strong hash function and secret seed, it appearsinfeasible for attackers to generate hash collisions because s and/or R areunknown</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6469</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">However, they can still observe the timings of data structureoperations for various m</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6470</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">With typical table sizes of 2^10 to 2^17 entries,attackers can detect some 'bin collisions'  inputs mapping to the same bin .Although this will be costly for the attacker, they can then send many instancesof such inputs, so we need to limit the resulting work for our data structure.Hash tables with separate chaining typically store bin entries in a linked list,so worst-case inputs lead to unacceptable linear-time lookup cost</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6471</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">We insteadseek optimal asymptotic worst-case complexity for each operation  insertion,deletion and lookups , which is a constant factor times the logarithm of thedata structure size</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6472</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">This naturally leads to a tree-like data structure for eachbin</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6473</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">The Java8 HashMap only replaces its linked list with trees when needed.This leads to additional cost and complexity for deciding whether a bin is alist or tree.Our first proposal  suggested by Github user funny-falcon  avoids this overheadby always storing one tree per bin</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6474</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">It may also be worthwhile to store the firstentry directly in the bin, which avoids allocating any tree nodes in the commoncase where bins are sparsely populated</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6475</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">What kind of tree should be used?Scapegoat and splay trees only offer amortized complexity guarantees, whereastreaps require an entropy source and have higher constant factors in practice.Self-balancing structures such as 2-3 or red-black trees require additionalbookkeeping information</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6476</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">We can hope to reduce rebalancing cost by realizingthat the output bits of strong H functions are uniformly distributed</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6477</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">Whenusing them as keys instead of the original message m, recent relaxed balancingschemes such as left-leaning red-black or weak AVL trees may require fewer treerotations to maintain their invariants</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6478</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">Note that H already determines thebin, so we should only use the remaining bits</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6479</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">64-bit hashes are likelysufficient for this purpose, and HighwayHash generates up to 256 bits</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6480</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">It seemsunlikely that attackers can craft inputs resulting in worst cases for both thebin index and tree key without being able to generate hash collisions, whichwould contradict the security claims of strong hashes</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6481</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">Even if they succeed, therelaxed tree balancing still guarantees an upper bound on height and thereforethe worst-case operation cost</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6482</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">For the AVL variant, the constant factors areslightly lower than for red-black trees.The second proposed approach uses augmented/de-amortized cuckoo hash tables These guarantee worst-case log n bounds for alloperations, but only if the hash function is 'indistinguishable from random' uniformly distributed regardless of the input distribution , which is claimedfor SipHash and HighwayHash but certainly not for weak hashes.Both alternatives retain good average case performance and defend againstflooding by limiting the amount of extra work an attacker can cause</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6483</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">The firstapproach guarantees an upper bound of log n additional work even if the hashfunction is compromised.In summary, a strong hash function is not, by itself, sufficient to protect achained hash table from flooding attacks</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6484</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">However, strong hash functions areimportant parts of two schemes for preventing denial of service</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6485</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Defending against hash flooding</field><field name="sentence">Using weak hashfunctions can slightly accelerate the best-case and average-case performance ofa service, but at the risk of greatly reduced attack costs and worst-case</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6486</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Third-party implementations / bindings</field><field name="sentence">Thanks to Damian Gryski and Frank Wessels for making us aware of thesethird-party implementations or bindings</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6487</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Third-party implementations / bindings</field><field name="sentence">Please feel free to get in touch orraise an issue and we'll add yours as well.By | Language | URLDamian Gryski | Go and x64 assembly | Lovell Fuller | node.js bindings | Vinzent Steinberg | Rust bindings | Frank Wessels & Andreas Auernhammer | Go and ARM assembly | Phil Demetriou | Python 3 bindings |</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6488</field><field name="title">google-highwayhash</field><field name="session">Hashes</field><field name="sentence">, updated 2017-12-29This is not an official Google product.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6489</field><field name="title">google-hilbert</field><field name="session">Hilbert     ! Coverage    ! Report card    ! GoDoc    ! Libraries.io</field><field name="sentence">Go package for mapping values to and from space-filling curves, such as Hilbert  and  Peano  curves.! Image of 8 by 8 Hilbert curve  images/hilbert.png  Documentation available here *This is not an official Google product  experimental or otherwise , it is just code that happens to be owned by Google.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6490</field><field name="title">google-hilbert</field><field name="session">Demo</field><field name="sentence">The demo directory contains an example on how to draw an images of Hilbert and Peano curves, as wellas animations of varying sizes for both.Simple 8x8 Hibert curve:! 8x8 Hilbert curve image  images/hilbert.png Simple 9x9 Peano curve:! 9x9 Hilbert curve image  images/peano.png Animation of Hibert curve with N in the range 1..8:! Hilbert curve animation  images/hilbert_animation.gif Animation of Peano curve with N in the range 1..6:! Peano curve animation  images/peano_animation.gif</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6491</field><field name="title">google-hilbert</field><field name="session">Licence  Apache 2</field><field name="sentence">Copyright 2015 Google Inc</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6492</field><field name="title">google-hilbert</field><field name="session">Licence  Apache 2</field><field name="sentence">All Rights Reserved.Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0  the "License" ;you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.You may obtain a copy of the License atdistributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.See the License for the specific language governing permissions andlimitations under the License.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6493</field><field name="title">google-homebrew-google-authenticator</field><field name="session">Homebrew formula for Google Authenticator</field><field name="sentence">Enables Google Authenticator as a two-factor authenticationfor Mac OS X ssh.for more information.> Caveat: As of August 2015 on Mac OS X El Capitan public beta clang crashes with a segfault.> A workaround is to install brew install gcc</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6494</field><field name="title">google-homebrew-google-authenticator</field><field name="session">Homebrew formula for Google Authenticator</field><field name="sentence">There is no pre-brewed bottle for> El Capitan yet, installation can take hours.>  see</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6495</field><field name="title">google-homebrew-xpra</field><field name="session">Homebrew formula for Xpra that works</field><field name="sentence">Formula is written from scratch to make it harder, better, faster, stronger.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6496</field><field name="title">google-homebrew-xpra</field><field name="session">Usage</field><field name="sentence">Add this repo as a tap brew tap timothybasanov/xpraInstall Xpra: brew install xpra  use can use --devel for 0.15.x branch Use Xpra as you usually do: xpra attach ssh:ubuntu.local:100</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6497</field><field name="title">google-homebrew-xpra</field><field name="session">Development process</field><field name="sentence">Clone this repo into /usr/local/Library/Tap/timothybasanov/Add as an IntelliJ projectEdit xpra.rbReinstall xpra: brew uninstall xpra ; brew install --verbose --debug --HEAD xpraI run live xpra server on a separate Ubuntu machine, here is how to debug xpra client:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6498</field><field name="title">google-honggfuzz</field><field name="session">Description</field><field name="sentence">A security oriented, feedback-driven, evolutionary, easy-to-use fuzzer with interesting analysis options</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6499</field><field name="title">google-honggfuzz</field><field name="session">Description</field><field name="sentence">See  USAGE  for the description of command-line options</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6500</field><field name="title">google-honggfuzz</field><field name="session">Code</field><field name="sentence">Honggfuzz has been used to find a few interesting security problems in major software packages; An incomplete list:The  examples directory contains code demonstrating  among others  how to use honggfuzz to find bugs in the OpenSSL library and in the  Apache HTTPD web server.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6501</field><field name="title">google-horenso</field><field name="session">ほー連想：探しやすいコードで漢字直接入力</field><field name="sentence">English is  here</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6502</field><field name="title">google-horenso</field><field name="session">漢字直接入力のメリット</field><field name="sentence">「きしゃ」など、漢字表記が多い読みを入力する場合、**長い候補リストで希望の漢字を探さなくても良いです。*</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6503</field><field name="title">google-horenso</field><field name="session">他の漢字直接入力システムに比べて【ほー連想】の長所</field><field name="sentence">JIS x 0213の全漢字に対応する予定で、対応するとしても三打鍵を超える入力コードを必要としません。規格の全漢字を網羅しているので**極わめて特殊な文章（例：漢文）を自然に入力することが出来ます。*かな入力コードが一般のローマ字かな入力と殆んど変わりません。</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6504</field><field name="title">google-horenso</field><field name="session">起動方法  Windows</field><field name="sentence">漢直Win をダウンロードして、zipを展開します。 ほー連想のテーブルファイル をダウンロードして、漢直Winのダイレクトリーにコピーします。 kanchoku.ini の、;outputUnicode=1の;を削除する必要があるかもしれません。これで、漢直Winの使い方とhrsの使い方が大体同じですが、漢直Winの場合はCaps Lockの代わりに、aを２回打って、カタカナモード・ひらがなモードのトグルができます。</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6505</field><field name="title">google-horenso</field><field name="session">キーボード配列を指定する</field><field name="sentence">リターンを押す度にテキストをコピーしたりどこかに送信するにはCOPY_TOOLの環境変数を指定します。リターンを押すと、このCOPY_TOOLが起動されSTDINにテキストが書き込まれます。例：Mac OS Xの場合、これをpbcopyに設定すると便利です。（<>をご参照ください）</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6506</field><field name="title">google-horenso</field><field name="session">コードの覚え方：かな</field><field name="sentence">コードは二打鍵：子音+母音になります。小文字 CAPS off にすると平仮名、大文字 CAPS on にすると片仮名になります。</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6507</field><field name="title">google-horenso</field><field name="session">コードの覚え方：漢字</field><field name="sentence">発音とは代表的と思われる音読み、国字や音読みがない漢字は訓読みです。使用可能なキーは aiueo の母音を除けば一鍵目のキーと同じです。印刷可能な 部首鍵＋読み鍵 早わかり表 もご利用になってください。印刷可能な 部首鍵＋読み鍵 早わかり表 もご利用になってください。のどれかになりますが、ｍとｘの両方を試すのを忘れないでください。（実際のコード配当されるので、二鍵目はｒです。フルコードはurp。</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6508</field><field name="title">google-horenso</field><field name="session">ファイルの説明</field><field name="sentence">ることができます。コードデータベース。行ごとに字と相対する入力コードがあります。コードを調べるには、このファイルを検索する方法もあります。未導入のJIS X 0213漢字も含まれていて、入力コードの代りにUCSコードポイントが明記されています。</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6509</field><field name="title">google-hotel-ads-etl-tool</field><field name="session">Hotel Ads ETL Tool</field><field name="sentence">This repository contains a tool that provides methods to extract informationfrom the  Hotel Ads API Reports  transform it using Dataflow/Apache Beam  and insert it into BigQuery tables in Google Cloud Platform.The tool is composed of the following parts:Alternatives: If needed, the python App Engine script can be modified to runlocally on a server or another orchestration system, as it doesn't depend onApp Engine to run</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6510</field><field name="title">google-hotel-ads-etl-tool</field><field name="session">Hotel Ads ETL Tool</field><field name="sentence">Also, the apache beam job can be run  after modifying thescript accordingly  in any managed or unmanaged Apache Beam instance.This is not an officially supported Google product.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6511</field><field name="title">google-hotel-ads-etl-tool</field><field name="session">Prerequisites</field><field name="sentence">Access to the Hotel Ads API</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6512</field><field name="title">google-hotel-ads-etl-tool</field><field name="session">Prerequisites</field><field name="sentence">Follow the steps of section "Setting upA Google Cloud Platform project, to hold the scripts and the data.Enable the Cloud Storage, BigQuery and Dataflow APIs.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6513</field><field name="title">google-hotel-ads-etl-tool</field><field name="session">Configuration Steps</field><field name="sentence">The configuration steps will be using the google cloud console, but it can alsobe run into a local server/workstation with the google cloud sdk installed.Login to GCP using gcloudCopy the file scripts/config.sh.sample to scripts/config.sh, andmodify the latter with the appropriated values:Copy the contents of the file scripts/config.sh to the indicated section in  # TODO: PASTE HERE THE CONTENTS OF THE scripts/config.sh FILEExecute the provisioning script autoprovision.sh</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6514</field><field name="title">google-hover</field><field name="session">Feature Updates:</field><field name="sentence">Demo Hover Menu ! Demo Hover Menu ! Demo Hover Menu Getting StartedTo get started with Hover, create a subclass of HoverMenuService to host your Hover menu</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6515</field><field name="title">google-hover</field><field name="session">Feature Updates:</field><field name="sentence">Implement onHoverMenuLaunched Intent, HoverView  to take control of your HoverView</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6516</field><field name="title">google-hover</field><field name="session">Feature Updates:</field><field name="sentence">You'll want to set it's HoverMenu, and also start it in the collapsed or expanded state:public class MyHoverMenuService extends HoverMenuService {</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6517</field><field name="title">google-hover</field><field name="session">Implement A HoverMenu</field><field name="sentence">A HoverMenu is the content that appears within a HoverView</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6518</field><field name="title">google-hover</field><field name="session">Implement A HoverMenu</field><field name="sentence">A HoverMenu is divided into an ordered list of Sections</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6519</field><field name="title">google-hover</field><field name="session">Implement A HoverMenu</field><field name="sentence">Each Section has a tab as well as Content that appear in your HoverView.If you want to create your own Hover Service from scratch, or if you want to experiment with a HoverView directly, you can instantiate one yourself.-----There is no built-in solution for this problem at this time</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6520</field><field name="title">google-hover</field><field name="session">Implement A HoverMenu</field><field name="sentence">You should take care to destroy your Hover Service when the HoverView is closed</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6521</field><field name="title">google-hover</field><field name="session">Implement A HoverMenu</field><field name="sentence">You may also want to inform the users of your app that issues with runtime permission dialogs might occur, and that those users should exit your Hover menu if problems occur.-------=======</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6522</field><field name="title">google-hpolyc</field><field name="session">HPolyC</field><field name="sentence">For many storage encryption applications, the ciphertext must be the same size as the plaintext;generally this matches the disk sector size of either 512 or 4096 bytes</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6523</field><field name="title">google-hpolyc</field><field name="session">HPolyC</field><field name="sentence">This means that standardapproaches like AES-GCM or RFC7539 cannot be applied</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6524</field><field name="title">google-hpolyc</field><field name="session">HPolyC</field><field name="sentence">The standard solution is AES-XTS, butthis has two disadvantages:HPolyC uses a fast polynomial hash  Poly1305  and a fast stream cipher  XChaCha12  to builda construction which encrypts an entire sector at a time</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6525</field><field name="title">google-hpolyc</field><field name="session">HPolyC</field><field name="sentence">Onan ARM Cortex-A7 processor, HPolyC decrypts 4096-byte messages at 14.5 cyclesper byte, over four times faster than AES-256-XTS</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6526</field><field name="title">google-hpolyc</field><field name="session">HPolyC</field><field name="sentence">HPolyC is also a "superpseudorandom permutation" over the whole sector, which means that any change to the plaintextof the sector results in an unrecognizably different ciphertext sector and vice versa.HPolyC is published as  ePrint report 2018/720 This repository includes:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6527</field><field name="title">google-http2preload</field><field name="session">http2preload</field><field name="sentence">A package for manipulating  HTTP/2 preload supporting  Google App Engine for Go See for a sample usage.Docs are available on godoc.org/github.com/google/http2preload</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6528</field><field name="title">google-http2preload</field><field name="session">License</field><field name="sentence">c  Google, Licensed under  Apache-2  LICENSE  license.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6529</field><field name="title">google-http_prefetching</field><field name="session">HTTP prefetching experiments</field><field name="sentence">**Disclaimer: This is not an official Google product.**This implements a proxy that injects prefetch hints, and a browser extensionthat prefetches pages based on received hints.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6530</field><field name="title">google-huproxy</field><field name="session">HUProxy</field><field name="sentence">Copyright 2017 Google Inc.This is not a Google product.HTTP S -Upgrade Proxy — Tunnel anything  but primarily SSH  over HTTP</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6531</field><field name="title">google-huproxy</field><field name="session">Why</field><field name="sentence">The reason for not simply using a SOCKS proxy or similar is that they tend totake up an entire port, while huproxy only takes up a single URL subdirectory.There's also SSL/SSH multiplexers but they:Take over the port and front both the web server and SSH, instead of lettingHide the original client address from the web server  without someOnly allow connecting to the server itself, not treat it as a proxy jumpgate.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6532</field><field name="title">google-huproxy</field><field name="session">Create user</field><field name="sentence">These commands assume that HTTPS is used</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6533</field><field name="title">google-huproxy</field><field name="session">Create user</field><field name="sentence">If not, then change "wss://"to "ws://".echo thomas:secretpassword > ~/.huproxy.pwchmod 600 ~/.huproxy.pwcat >> ~/.ssh/config << EOFHost shell.example.comssh shell.example.comOr manually with these commands:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6534</field><field name="title">google-hyou</field><field name="session">Login to Google Spreadsheet with credentials</field><field name="sentence">collection = hyou.login '/path/to/credentails.json'</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6535</field><field name="title">google-hyou</field><field name="session">Open a spreadsheet by ID</field><field name="sentence">spreadsheet = collection '1ZYeIFccacgHkL0TPfdgXiMfPCuEEWUtbhXvaB9HBDzQ' print spreadsheet.title</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6536</field><field name="title">google-hyou</field><field name="session">Open a worksheet in a spreadsheet by sheet name</field><field name="sentence">worksheet = spreadsheet 'Sheet1' print worksheet.titleprint worksheet.rowsprint worksheet.cols</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6537</field><field name="title">google-hyou</field><field name="session">Worksheet objects can be accessed just like two-dimensional lists</field><field name="sentence">print worksheet 1  0 print worksheet 1  1</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6538</field><field name="title">google-hyou</field><field name="session">Call Worksheet.commit   to apply changes</field><field name="sentence">worksheet 2  0  = 'cinamon'worksheet 2  1  = 40worksheet.commit  -------------Documentation is available atShuhei TakahashiThis library is authored by a Googler and copyrighted by Google, butis not an official Google product.-------Copyright 2015 Google Inc</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6539</field><field name="title">google-hyou</field><field name="session">Call Worksheet.commit   to apply changes</field><field name="sentence">All Rights Reserved.Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0  the "License" ;you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.You may obtain a copy of the License atdistributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.See the License for the specific language governing permissions andlimitations under the License.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6540</field><field name="title">google-hypebot</field><field name="session">HypeBot</field><field name="sentence">HypeBot is the perfect way to add more #Hype to your chat application</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6541</field><field name="title">google-hypebot</field><field name="session">HypeBot</field><field name="sentence">Simplyadd this bot to get #Hype.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6542</field><field name="title">google-hypebot</field><field name="session">Development Guide</field><field name="sentence">Want to increase #HypeQuality? Join  to get started.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6543</field><field name="title">google-hypebot</field><field name="session">Running the Bot</field><field name="sentence">Use bazel for building all the things</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6544</field><field name="title">google-hypebot</field><field name="session">Running the Bot</field><field name="sentence">Installation instructions</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6545</field><field name="title">google-hypebot</field><field name="session">Running the Bot</field><field name="sentence">Discord is our primary chat application interface</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6546</field><field name="title">google-hypebot</field><field name="session">Running the Bot</field><field name="sentence">Create  anapplication with Discord</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6547</field><field name="title">google-hypebot</field><field name="session">Running the Bot</field><field name="sentence">Once the application is created, click "Create A BotUser" to get a Discord Token</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6548</field><field name="title">google-hypebot</field><field name="session">Running the Bot</field><field name="sentence">You then need admin privilegeson a server and select "Generate OAuth2 URL" to invite the bot to your server.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6549</field><field name="title">google-hypebot</field><field name="session">Weather Key</field><field name="sentence">HypeBot gets its weather from www.apixu.com</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6550</field><field name="title">google-hypebot</field><field name="session">Weather Key</field><field name="sentence">Signup  to get your key.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6551</field><field name="title">google-hypebot</field><field name="session">Storage</field><field name="sentence">By default, HypeBot looks for a Redis server running on localhost at the defaultport  You can pass overrides in --params to use a different location.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6552</field><field name="title">google-hypebot</field><field name="session">Riot</field><field name="sentence">To integrate with the Riot API, you need to  create anapplication  in order to get an API</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6553</field><field name="title">google-hypebot</field><field name="session">Type Annotations</field><field name="sentence">HypeBot is joining the 21st century and attempting to use a new fancy typeannotation or hinting library to reduce the number of bugs that careless humansintroduce into the otherwise spotless codebase</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6554</field><field name="title">google-hypebot</field><field name="session">Type Annotations</field><field name="sentence">As you modify existing code oradd new functionality, please use typing  Since we only supportpython3, this can be done in two easy steps</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6555</field><field name="title">google-hypebot</field><field name="session">Type Annotations</field><field name="sentence">Add the relevant imports from the typing module into your python file Add type annotations to your function definitions</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6556</field><field name="title">google-hypebot</field><field name="session">Type Annotations</field><field name="sentence">As an example:A few "best" practices:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6557</field><field name="title">google-hypebot</field><field name="session">What about HypeParams?</field><field name="sentence">Because of how HypeParams operates  specifically, creating attributesdynamically from the initialization dict , typing can't provide usefultype-checking to these objects</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6558</field><field name="title">google-hypebot</field><field name="session">What about HypeParams?</field><field name="sentence">If you need to annotate a HypeParams instance,just use Any as per the best practices above.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6559</field><field name="title">google-hypebot</field><field name="session">Legal</field><field name="sentence">Hypebot is not an official Google product.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6560</field><field name="title">google-idaidle</field><field name="session">idaidle</field><field name="sentence">Copyright 2016-2018 Google LLCDisclaimer: This is not an official Google product  experimental or otherwise ,it is just code that happens to be owned by Google.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6561</field><field name="title">google-idaidle</field><field name="session">What is it?</field><field name="sentence">idaidle is a plugin for the commercial IDA Pro disassembler that warns users ifthey leave their instance idling for too long</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6562</field><field name="title">google-idaidle</field><field name="session">What is it?</field><field name="sentence">After a predetermined amount ofidle time, the plugin first warns and later then saves the current disassemlbydatabase and closes IDA.This is useful in organizations with IDA Pro floating licenses to make surethat analysts return their license to the license server when they are doneusing it.path of your IDA SDK installation:To configure for 32-bit IDA  IDA 6.95 or lower, or IDA 7.0 "old_x86" , usethe IDA 6.95 SDK and the following commands instead:Once configured, start the build with:If all goes well, depending on your configuration, the following plugin filesare now in the build directory:| OS| ------| Linux   | idaidle.so| macOS   | idaidle.dylib| Windows | idaidle.dllNote: A 64 in anywhere in any of the filenames denotes a 64-bit addressaware plugin.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6563</field><field name="title">google-idaidle</field><field name="session">Installation</field><field name="sentence">To install system-wide, put the plugin binaries into the plugins folderin your IDA Pro installation</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6564</field><field name="title">google-idaidle</field><field name="session">Installation</field><field name="sentence">Below are the default paths:| OS| ------| Linux   | /opt/ida-7.0/plugins| macOS   | /Applications/IDA Pro 7.0/idabin/plugins  || Windows | %ProgramFiles x86 %\IDA 7.0\pluginsReplace 7.0 with your actual version number.To install just for the current user, copy the files into one of thesedirectories instead:| OS| ----------| Linux/macOS | ~/.idapro/plugins| Windows</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6565</field><field name="title">google-idaidle</field><field name="session">Usage</field><field name="sentence">As soon as a database is opened, the plugin starts to monitor idle time, i.e.the time between to consecutive UI operations</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6566</field><field name="title">google-idaidle</field><field name="session">Usage</field><field name="sentence">By default, after six hours,a warning is printed to the output window</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6567</field><field name="title">google-idaidle</field><field name="session">Usage</field><field name="sentence">After 12 hours, a databasesnapshot will be created and the IDA Pro instance will be closed withoutsaving</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6568</field><field name="title">google-idaidle</field><field name="session">Usage</field><field name="sentence">This is so that the plugin does not accidentally overwrite unsavedwork or databases the analyst did not want to save.There is no configuration file, but the following command-line options are| Option| --------------------------| -OIdaIdleWarningSeconds:N | Warn the user after _N_ seconds of inactivity  || -OIdaIdleTimeoutSeconds:N | Create snapshot and close IDA afer _N_ seconds |Note: IDA only recognizes these command-line options if they come _before_ any</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6569</field><field name="title">google-identity-aware-prober</field><field name="session">Identity Aware Prober</field><field name="sentence">Identity Aware Prober  iaprober  is a binary intended to be used as an externalserver-mode probe for use with  Cloudprober  for probing pagesbehind Google Cloud's  Identity Aware Proxy  IAP  The binary reads GCP service account credentials from a local JSON file</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6570</field><field name="title">google-identity-aware-prober</field><field name="session">Identity Aware Prober</field><field name="sentence">That serviceaccount must have read access to the IAP-protected page.DISCLAIMER: This is not an officially supported Google product</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6571</field><field name="title">google-identity-aware-prober</field><field name="session">How to use iaprober</field><field name="sentence">The easiest way to use iaprober is to run it alongside Cloudprober in Docker,in Google Kubernetes Engine</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6572</field><field name="title">google-identity-aware-prober</field><field name="session">How to use iaprober</field><field name="sentence">Note: the following commands enable chargeable APIsand services on Google Cloud Platform.The following assumes you have an existing Google Cloud project.To create a new service account, follow the instructions for  creating a newaccount Grant this service account permission to access any IAP-protected page that youwant to test.To create a new Kubernetes cluster, following the instructions for  creating acluster This will also configure your local kubectl command.Download the service account's credentials as a .json file, following theinstructions at  creating and managing service accountkeys Put the credentials in a file named auth.json</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6573</field><field name="title">google-identity-aware-prober</field><field name="session">How to use iaprober</field><field name="sentence">Upload this to your Kubernetescluster as a secret:space-separated parameters:A short-name for the page you are testingThe OAuth client-id for the IAP page</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6574</field><field name="title">google-identity-aware-prober</field><field name="session">How to use iaprober</field><field name="sentence">This can be found on theThis file should be uploaded as a Kubernetes ConfigMap resource:Cloudprober container, and the Cloudprober container is based upon Busybox, wewon't have shared libraries available</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6575</field><field name="title">google-identity-aware-prober</field><field name="session">How to use iaprober</field><field name="sentence">The makefile specifies the necessarybuild flags to create a static binary that will work on Busybox.project name :Add the live tag to the container image:iaprober container to gcr.io/${GOOGLE_CLOUD_PROJECT}/identity-aware-prober:liveDeploy the service and expose the Prometheus metrics port:cloudprober.yaml, and run kubectl apply -f cloudprober.yaml</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6576</field><field name="title">google-identity-aware-prober</field><field name="session">Running iaprober manually</field><field name="sentence">If running cloudprober manually, you'll need the iaprober binary, and theservice account credentials available locally</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6577</field><field name="title">google-identity-aware-prober</field><field name="session">Running iaprober manually</field><field name="sentence">Modify the followingcloudprober.cfg file as appropriate:For a one-off test you can run iaprober from the command line</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6578</field><field name="title">google-identity-aware-prober</field><field name="session">Running iaprober manually</field><field name="sentence">You will need theservice account JSON credentials, the OAuth client ID of the IAP page, and the</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6579</field><field name="title">google-identity-toolkit-go-client</field><field name="session">Google Identity Toolkit Go client</field><field name="sentence">The credentials returned aredetermined by the environment the code is running in</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6580</field><field name="title">google-identity-toolkit-go-client</field><field name="session">Google Identity Toolkit Go client</field><field name="sentence">Conditions are checked inthe following order:The environment variable GOOGLE_APPLICATION_CREDENTIALS is checked</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6581</field><field name="title">google-identity-toolkit-go-client</field><field name="session">Google Identity Toolkit Go client</field><field name="sentence">If thisvariable is specified it should point to a file that defines the credentials.The simplest way to get a credential for this purpose is to create a serviceaccount using the Google Developers Console in the section APIs & Auth, in thesub-section Credentials</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6582</field><field name="title">google-identity-toolkit-go-client</field><field name="session">Google Identity Toolkit Go client</field><field name="sentence">Create a service account or choose an existing one andselect Generate new JSON key</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6583</field><field name="title">google-identity-toolkit-go-client</field><field name="session">Google Identity Toolkit Go client</field><field name="sentence">Set the environment variable to the path of theJSON file downloaded.If you have installed the Google Cloud SDK on your machine and have run thecommand gcloud auth login, your identity can be used as a proxy to test codecalling APIs from that machine.If you are running in Google App Engine production, the built-in serviceaccount associated with the application will be used.If you are running in Google Compute Engine production, the built-inservice account associated with the virtual machine instance will be used.If none of these conditions is true, an error will occur.If Application Default Credentials doesn't work for your use case, you canset GoogleAppCredentialsPath in the config to the JSON key file path</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6584</field><field name="title">google-identity-toolkit-go-client</field><field name="session">Google Identity Toolkit Go client</field><field name="sentence">travisimg :  travis :  gitkit :  gadc :</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6585</field><field name="title">google-identity-toolkit-php-client</field><field name="session">Google Identity Toolkit client library for PHP</field><field name="sentence">This is the PHP client library for Google Identity Toolkit services.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6586</field><field name="title">google-identity-toolkit-php-client</field><field name="session">Example Code</field><field name="sentence">require_once __DIR__</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6587</field><field name="title">google-identity-toolkit-php-client</field><field name="session">Example Code</field><field name="sentence">'/vendor/autoload.php';$gitkitClient = Gitkit_Client::createFromFile "gitkit-server-config.json" ;// ---$hashKey = "\x01\x02\x03";$gitkitClient->uploadUsers 'HMAC_SHA1', $hashKey, createNewUsers $hashKey  ;// --$user = $gitkitClient->validateToken "eyJhb..." ;// ---$user = $gitkitClient->getUserById "1234" ;// ---$verificationLink = $gitkitClient->getEmailVerificationLink "1234@example.com" ;// ---$iterator = $gitkitClient->getAllUsers 3 ;while  $iterator->valid    {  $user = $iterator->current  ;  // $user is a Gitkit_Account object  $iterator->next  ;// ---$gitkitClient->deleteUser '1234' ;function createNewUsers $hashKey  {  $allUsers = array  ;  $gitkitUser->setEmail "1234@example.com" ;  $gitkitUser->setUserId "1234" ;  $salt = "\05\06\07";  $password = '1111';  $gitkitUser->setSalt $salt ;  $gitkitUser->setPasswordHash hash_hmac 'sha1', $password</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6588</field><field name="title">google-identity-toolkit-php-client</field><field name="session">Example Code</field><field name="sentence">$salt, $hashKey, true  ;  array_push $allUsers, $gitkitUser ;  $gitkitUser->setEmail '5678@example.com' ;  $gitkitUser->setUserId '5678' ;  $salt = "\15\16\17";  $password = '5555';  $gitkitUser->setSalt $salt ;  $gitkitUser->setPasswordHash hash_hmac 'sha1', $password</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6589</field><field name="title">google-identity-toolkit-php-client</field><field name="session">Example Code</field><field name="sentence">$salt, $hashKey, true  ;  array_push $allUsers, $gitkitUser ;</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6590</field><field name="title">google-idris-protobuf</field><field name="session">A partial implementation of Protocol Buffers in Idris</field><field name="sentence">Protocol buffers are a serializable format for structured data that isubiquitous at Google</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6591</field><field name="title">google-idris-protobuf</field><field name="session">A partial implementation of Protocol Buffers in Idris</field><field name="sentence">Idris is a language where types are first class valuesthat is useful for theorem proving and metaprogramming</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6592</field><field name="title">google-idris-protobuf</field><field name="session">A partial implementation of Protocol Buffers in Idris</field><field name="sentence">This package contains apartial implementation of protocol buffers in the Idris language</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6593</field><field name="title">google-idris-protobuf</field><field name="session">A partial implementation of Protocol Buffers in Idris</field><field name="sentence">The goal isto demonstrate how Idris is capable of advanced metaprogramming that simplifiesthe implementation of protocol buffers.Protocol buffers are a way to describe a schema for serializable data</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6594</field><field name="title">google-idris-protobuf</field><field name="session">A partial implementation of Protocol Buffers in Idris</field><field name="sentence">Theschema is called a protocol buffer "message"</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6595</field><field name="title">google-idris-protobuf</field><field name="session">A partial implementation of Protocol Buffers in Idris</field><field name="sentence">A message describes the kind ofdata that is to be serialized, and comprises a set of fields</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6596</field><field name="title">google-idris-protobuf</field><field name="session">A partial implementation of Protocol Buffers in Idris</field><field name="sentence">Each field can bea primitive type, an enum, or another message</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6597</field><field name="title">google-idris-protobuf</field><field name="session">A partial implementation of Protocol Buffers in Idris</field><field name="sentence">In this way protocol buffersallow the description of arbitrary data types</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6598</field><field name="title">google-idris-protobuf</field><field name="session">A partial implementation of Protocol Buffers in Idris</field><field name="sentence">Below is shown a protocolmessage describing a phone number, including an enum definition for the typeof a phone number  mobile, home or work .In most languages, protocol buffers are turned into native data types by codegeneration</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6599</field><field name="title">google-idris-protobuf</field><field name="session">A partial implementation of Protocol Buffers in Idris</field><field name="sentence">E.g</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6600</field><field name="title">google-idris-protobuf</field><field name="session">A partial implementation of Protocol Buffers in Idris</field><field name="sentence">in C++, the generated code for the Person class will bea C++ class with methods like set_name, name and more complex method toset nested messages like phone</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6601</field><field name="title">google-idris-protobuf</field><field name="session">A partial implementation of Protocol Buffers in Idris</field><field name="sentence">The code is generated by a compiler thattakes protocol message descriptions like the one above, parses them and emitsgenerated C++ code.However in Idris, we can avoid generating code by considering a type ofmessage descriptors  so the Person message description would be an value withthis type</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6602</field><field name="title">google-idris-protobuf</field><field name="session">A partial implementation of Protocol Buffers in Idris</field><field name="sentence">This is the MessageDescriptor class</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6603</field><field name="title">google-idris-protobuf</field><field name="session">A partial implementation of Protocol Buffers in Idris</field><field name="sentence">In the protocol buffersdocumentation this is just called a Descriptor but here it's useful to bemore consistent in naming</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6604</field><field name="title">google-idris-protobuf</field><field name="session">A partial implementation of Protocol Buffers in Idris</field><field name="sentence">The unique property of Idris is that we candefine an inductive data type InterpMessage which has MessageDescriptor forits index space, so that InterpMessage Person is the type of messages oftype Person</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6605</field><field name="title">google-idris-protobuf</field><field name="session">A partial implementation of Protocol Buffers in Idris</field><field name="sentence">Inductive data types are similar to C++ templates but with theadvantage their arguments can be any value and that value need not even beknown at compile time.In Idris we can write generic, type safe, code for working with protocolbuffers</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6606</field><field name="title">google-idris-protobuf</field><field name="session">A partial implementation of Protocol Buffers in Idris</field><field name="sentence">In particular we have code for serialization and deserialization toand from text form</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6607</field><field name="title">google-idris-protobuf</field><field name="session">A partial implementation of Protocol Buffers in Idris</field><field name="sentence">Serialization looks likeNote that this function is generic in that d ranges over the space ofmessage descriptors, and for each d, the type of the second argument isa message of type InterpMessage d, that is a protocol message in the formatgiven by the descriptor d</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6608</field><field name="title">google-idris-protobuf</field><field name="session">A partial implementation of Protocol Buffers in Idris</field><field name="sentence">Deserialization can also be done generically.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6609</field><field name="title">google-idris-protobuf</field><field name="session">About this Repo</field><field name="sentence">The main purpose of the repo is to demonstrate and explore some interestingapplications of Idris</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6610</field><field name="title">google-idris-protobuf</field><field name="session">About this Repo</field><field name="sentence">Most of the interesting applications are in the Testdirectory which contains an example descriptor Person along with someexamples of creating an instance of InterpMessage Person and some methodsto inspect properties.The PhoneType : EnumDescriptorPhoneType = MkEnumDescriptor    MkEnumValueDescriptor "MOBILE" 0,  MkEnumValueDescriptor "HOME" 1,  MkEnumValueDescriptor "WORK" 5 PhoneNumber : MessageDescriptorPhoneNumber = MkMessageDescriptor    MkFieldDescriptor Required PBString "number",  MkFieldDescriptor Optional  PBEnum PhoneType  "type" Person : MessageDescriptorPerson = MkMessageDescriptor    MkFieldDescriptor Required PBString "name",  MkFieldDescriptor Required PBInt32 "id",  MkFieldDescriptor Optional PBString "email",  MkFieldDescriptor Repeated  PBMessage PhoneNumber  "phone" Note that the MkMessage constructor accepts a heterogeneous list</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6611</field><field name="title">google-idris-protobuf</field><field name="session">About this Repo</field><field name="sentence">This isnot an HVect but a data type we construct in Protobuf.idr whose constructorsare Nil and  :: , but whose elements have types corresponding to thetypes of the fields given by the message descriptor.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6612</field><field name="title">google-idris-protobuf</field><field name="session">Install the  Lightyear  package.</field><field name="sentence">This can be done by cloning the repo by running this command from your home</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6613</field><field name="title">google-idris-protobuf</field><field name="session">Clone this repo and run the tests.</field><field name="sentence">Clone this repo by running the following from your home directory</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6614</field><field name="title">google-idris-protobuf</field><field name="session">Experiment in the REPL.</field><field name="sentence">In order to load the repl with this package, first install it with the command</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6615</field><field name="title">google-ijaas</field><field name="session">IntelliJ as a Service</field><field name="sentence">Make IntelliJ as a Java server that does autocompletion for Vim.This is not an official Google product  i.e</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6616</field><field name="title">google-ijaas</field><field name="session">IntelliJ as a Service</field><field name="sentence">a 20% project .</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6617</field><field name="title">google-ijaas</field><field name="session">Installation</field><field name="sentence">git clone.Import project into IntelliJ</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6618</field><field name="title">google-ijaas</field><field name="session">Installation</field><field name="sentence">Use Gradle plugin.Run gradle buildPlugin</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6619</field><field name="title">google-ijaas</field><field name="session">Installation</field><field name="sentence">It creates build/distributions/ijaas-*.zip at theSelect "File" menu and click "Settings..."</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6620</field><field name="title">google-ijaas</field><field name="session">Installation</field><field name="sentence">In "Plugins" menu, click "InstallRestart IntelliJ.Add "vim" directory to your runtimepath in Vim in your own way.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6621</field><field name="title">google-ijaas</field><field name="session">Development</field><field name="sentence">If you want to isolate your development version and the current version, youmight need two clones</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6622</field><field name="title">google-ijaas</field><field name="session">Development</field><field name="sentence">You can load Vim plugins conditionally by usingenvironment variables.port  see Connect to the testing IntelliJ with USE_DEV_IJAAS=1 IJAAS_PORT=5801 vim</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6623</field><field name="title">google-ijaas</field><field name="session">Development</field><field name="sentence">Theijaas vim plugin will recognize IJAAS_PORT and use that to connect to theijaas IntelliJ plugin.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6624</field><field name="title">google-image-compression</field><field name="session">#image-compression</field><field name="sentence">This repository contains an image compression library that provides routinesfor converting to and from various compressed image formats, such as DXT, ETC,and PVRTC.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6625</field><field name="title">google-image-rebase</field><field name="session">Docker Image Rebase</field><field name="sentence">This tool rewrites an image's manifest to replace layers in a base image withlayers in another version of that base image</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6626</field><field name="title">google-image-rebase</field><field name="session">Docker Image Rebase</field><field name="sentence">It does so entirely with API callsto the registry, so it doesn't have to download or upload full layer blobs atany point.This can be useful if you want to produce container images with security or bugfixes in base images, without having to completely rebuild the image fromsource</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6627</field><field name="title">google-image-rebase</field><field name="session">Docker Image Rebase</field><field name="sentence">For instance, you might not have access to the original source anymore,or you want to produce updated images without performing a full rebuild.cases</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6628</field><field name="title">google-image-rebase</field><field name="session">Docker Image Rebase</field><field name="sentence">More details below, but caveat emptor.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6629</field><field name="title">google-image-rebase</field><field name="session">Using image-rebase</field><field name="sentence">For purposes of illustration, imagine you've built a container imagegcr.io/my-project/my-app:latest, containing your app, and based on some OSimage, for instance, launcher.gcr.io/google/ubuntu16_04</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6630</field><field name="title">google-image-rebase</field><field name="session">Using image-rebase</field><field name="sentence">A vulnerability hasbeen found in the base image, and a new fixed version has been released.You could build your app image again, and its FROMlauncher.gcr.io/google/ubuntu16_04 directive would pick up the new base imagerelease, but that requires a full rebuild of your entire app from source, whichmight pull in other changes in dependencies</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6631</field><field name="title">google-image-rebase</field><field name="session">Using image-rebase</field><field name="sentence">You just want to release thiscritical bug fix, as quickly as possible.Instead, you could use this tool to replace the vulnerable base image layers inyour image with new patched base image layers from the newly released baseimage, without needing to rebuild from source, or indeed have access to thesource at all.check that old_base is indeed the basis for original, remove old_base'slayers from original and replace them with new_base's layers, then computeand upload a new valid manifest for the image, tagged as rebased.If the image is in Google Container Registry, you can determine old_base imagedigests using gcloud alpha container images describe</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6632</field><field name="title">google-image-rebase</field><field name="session">Rebase visualized</field><field name="sentence">! rebase visualization  ./rebase.png</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6633</field><field name="title">google-image-rebase</field><field name="session">Installing image-rebase</field><field name="sentence">The tool can be installed using go get:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6634</field><field name="title">google-image-rebase</field><field name="session">Rebase as a Go library</field><field name="sentence">You can also use the image-rebase logic as a library in your Go program, byimporting it:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6635</field><field name="title">google-image-rebase</field><field name="session">Caveats</field><field name="sentence">Rebasing has no visibility into what the container image contains, or whatconstitutes a "valid" image</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6636</field><field name="title">google-image-rebase</field><field name="session">Caveats</field><field name="sentence">As a result, it's perfectly capable of producing animage that's entirely invalid garbage</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6637</field><field name="title">google-image-rebase</field><field name="session">Caveats</field><field name="sentence">Rebasing arbitrary layers in an image isnot a good idea.To help prevent garbage images, rebasing should only be done at a point in thelayer stack between "base" layers and "app" layers</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6638</field><field name="title">google-image-rebase</field><field name="session">Caveats</field><field name="sentence">These should adhere to somecontract about what "base" layers can be expected to produce, and what "app"layers should expect from base layers.In the example above, for instance, we assume that the "Ubuntu" base image isadhering to some contract with downstream app layers, that it won't remove ordrastically change what it provides to the app layer</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6639</field><field name="title">google-image-rebase</field><field name="session">Caveats</field><field name="sentence">If the new_base layersremoved some installed package, or made a breaking change to the version of somecompiler expected by the uppermost app layers, the resulting rebased image mightbe invalid.In general, it's a good practice to tag rebased images to some other tag thanthe original tag once it's determined the image is valid.There is ongoing work to standardize and advertise base image contractadherence to make rebasing safer.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6640</field><field name="title">google-image-rebase</field><field name="session">Automatic Rebase Seam Detection</field><field name="sentence">If an app image adheres to a strong contract with its base layers, the toolthat builds the app image can insert a hint into the image, in the form of a--new_base automatically.The form of the LABEL is:in --old_base= and --new_base=.In this way, new releases of  will automatically be consideredas --new_base for the app image, if the flags aren't passed explicitly.The image-rebase tool injects this LABEL into the --rebased image itproduces, if --new_base is passed as a tag, to aid future rebase operationson that image.Using the example above, gcr.io/my-project/my-app:rebased contains the following label:Future rebase operations can be specified with just two flags:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6641</field><field name="title">google-import-mailbox-to-gmail</field><field name="session">Import .mbox files to G Suite  formerly Google Apps for Work</field><field name="sentence">This script allows G Suite admins to import mbox files in bulk for their**DISCLAIMER**: This is not an official Google product.If you want to migrate from Mozilla Thunderbird, try mail-importer You only authorize it once using a service account, and then it can import mailinto the mailboxes of all users in your domain.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6642</field><field name="title">google-import-mailbox-to-gmail</field><field name="session">A. Creating and authorizing a service account for Gmail API</field><field name="sentence">Go to the  Developers Console Create a new project.Click the **Enable and manage APIs*Enable the Gmail APIClick the 3-line icon  **≡**  in the top left corner of the console.Click **IAM & Admin*Click **Create service account**.Enter a name  for example, "import-mailbox"  in the **Name*Check the **Furnish a new private key*Check the **Enable G Suite Domain-wide Delegation*Click **Create**</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6643</field><field name="title">google-import-mailbox-to-gmail</field><field name="session">A. Creating and authorizing a service account for Gmail API</field><field name="sentence">You will see a confirmation message advising that theClick **Close**.Click the **View Client ID*Copy the **Client ID*Go to  the **Manage API client access*Under **One or More API Scopes**, enter the following:Click **Authorize**.You can now use the JSON file to authorize programs to access the Gmail API"insert" and "label" scopes of all users in your G Suite domain.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6644</field><field name="title">google-import-mailbox-to-gmail</field><field name="session">B. Importing mbox files using import-mailbox-to-gmail.py</field><field name="sentence">**Important**: If you're planning to import mail from Apple Mail.app, see the notes below.Download the script  Download  and install Python 2.7  notOpen a **Command Prompt*Install the Google API Client Libraries for Python and their dependencies byCreate a folder for the mbox files, for example C:\mbox.Under that folder, create a folder for each of the users into which youInto each of the folders, copy the mbox files for that user</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6645</field><field name="title">google-import-mailbox-to-gmail</field><field name="session">B. Importing mbox files using import-mailbox-to-gmail.py</field><field name="sentence">Make sure the  C:\mbox  C:\mbox\user1@domain.com  C:\mbox\user1@domain.com\Imported messages.mbox  C:\mbox\user1@domain.com\Other imported messages.mbox  C:\mbox\user2@domain.com  C:\mbox\user2@domain.com\Imported messages.mbox  C:\mbox\user2@domain.com\Other imported messages.mbox    users' mailboxes</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6646</field><field name="title">google-import-mailbox-to-gmail</field><field name="session">B. Importing mbox files using import-mailbox-to-gmail.py</field><field name="sentence">First, migrate the mbox files into a test user, to make sure  the messages are imported correctly.To start the migration, run the following command  one line :can monitor the migration by looking at the output, and inspect errors byviewing the import-mailbox-to-gmail.log file.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6647</field><field name="title">google-import-mailbox-to-gmail</field><field name="session">Options and notes</field><field name="sentence">_all_ users and _all_ mbox files</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6648</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">In silico labeling: Predicting fluorescent labels in unlabeled images</field><field name="sentence">This is the code forIn silico labeling: Predicting fluorescent labels inunlabeled images</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6649</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">In silico labeling: Predicting fluorescent labels in unlabeled images</field><field name="sentence">It is the result of a collaboration between  Google AcceleratedScience  and two external labs: the  LeeRubin lab  at Harvard and the  StevenFinkbeiner lab  atGladstone</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6650</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">In silico labeling: Predicting fluorescent labels in unlabeled images</field><field name="sentence">See also  our blog post  and our  full dataset, including many predictions we couldn't fit in the paper  data.md .This code in this repository can be used to run training and inference of ourmodel on a single machine, and can be adapted for distributed training</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6651</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">In silico labeling: Predicting fluorescent labels in unlabeled images</field><field name="sentence">It also contains a set of weights created by trainingthe model on the data in Conditions A, B, C, and D from the paper.This README will explain how to: Restore the model from the provided checkpoint and run inference on an image Train the pre-trained model on a new dataset  Condition E .Please note, the example in this README deviates from the way transfer learning is demonstrated in the paper.In the paper, the model is trained once on all datasets, including Condition E; this is also called multi-task learning.In this guide, we're starting with a pre-trained model on Conditions A, B, C, and D, and incrementally training it on Condition E.The benefit of the latter technique is it requires less time to learn a new task, but it is likely to overfit if overtrained  see below .The model here differs from the model described in the paper in one significantway: this model does an initial linear projection to 16 features per pixel,where the model in the paper does not have this step</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6652</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">In silico labeling: Predicting fluorescent labels in unlabeled images</field><field name="sentence">This allows the model totake as input *z*-stacks with varying numbers of *zneeds to be relearned is the initial linear projection</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6653</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">In silico labeling: Predicting fluorescent labels in unlabeled images</field><field name="sentence">Here, we'll use it totake full advantage of the 26 *zhave 13 *zYou can also find the complete set of preprocessed data used for the paper,along with predictions,  here  data.md .*This is not an official Google product.*</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6654</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Code</field><field name="sentence">The code requires Python 3 and depends on NumPy, TensorFlow, and OpenCV</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6655</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Code</field><field name="sentence">You caninstall TensorFlow using  this guide which will also install NumPy</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6656</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Code</field><field name="sentence">If you follow that guide you will have installedpip3 and you'll be able to install OpenCV with the command: pip3 install--upgrade opencv-python.We're using  Bazel  to build the code and run tests.Though not strictly necessary, we suggest you install it  the rest of thisREADME will assume you have it .This code has been tested in Debian 10 with TensorFlow 1.9 on a machine with 64 GB RAM.It is not optimized for memory use, and has been reported to fail with a Python MemoryError on a machine with 16 GB RAM.Based on tests with ulimit, we recommend using a machine with at least 32 GB RAM.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6657</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Data</field><field name="sentence">We'll work with the data sample in  data_sample.zip  Warning: 2 GB download  and a checkpoint from the pre-trained modelin  checkpoints.zip  Ifyou have  gsutil  installed, you can also use the commands:The rest of this README will assume you've downloaded and extracted thesearchives to checkpoints/ and data_sample/.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6658</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Running the pre-trained model.</field><field name="sentence">Training and inference are controlled by the script isl/launch.py</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6659</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Running the pre-trained model.</field><field name="sentence">We recommendyou invoke the script with Bazel  see below , because it will handle dependencymanagement for you.The checkpoints.zip file contains parameters from a model trained onConditions A, B, C, and D</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6660</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Running the pre-trained model.</field><field name="sentence">To run the model on a sample from Condition B, runthis command from the project root:If you get a syntax error, make sure you're using Python 3, not Python In the above: BASE_DIRECTORY is the working directory for the model</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6661</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Running the pre-trained model.</field><field name="sentence">It will be created alsologtostderr will cause progress information to be printed to the stitch_crop_size is the size of the crop for which we'll perform infer_channel_whitelist is the list of fluorescence channels we wish toIf you run this command, you should get a target_error_panel.png that lookslike this:Each row is one of the whitelisted channels you provided; in this case it's onerow for each of the DAPI_CONFOCAL, MAP2_CONFOCAL, and NFH_CONFOCAL channels</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6662</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Running the pre-trained model.</field><field name="sentence">The boxes with thepurple borders show the predicted images  in this case the medians of theper-pixel distributions</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6663</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Running the pre-trained model.</field><field name="sentence">The boxes with the teal borders show the truefluorescence images</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6664</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Running the pre-trained model.</field><field name="sentence">The boxes with the black borders show errors, with falsepositives in orange and false negatives in blue.The script will also generate a file called  input_error_panel.png  which showsthe 26 transmitted light input images along with auto-encoding predictions anderrors</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6665</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Running the pre-trained model.</field><field name="sentence">For this condition, there were only 13 *z*-depths, so this visualizationwill show each *z*-depth twice.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6666</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Training the pre-trained model on a new dataset.</field><field name="sentence">Condition E contains a cell type not previously seen by the model  human cancercells , imaged with a transmitted light modality not previously seen  DIC , andlabeled with a marker not previously seen  CellMask .We have two wells in our sample data  B2 and B3 , so let's use B2 for training and B3 for evaluation.To see how well the model can predict labels on the evaluation dataset *beforeThis should produce this target error panel:This is like the error panels above, but the first row is DAPI_CONFOCAL and the second is CELLMASK_CONFOCAL.And because we used noinfer_simplify_error_panels it includes more statistics of thepixel distribution</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6667</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Training the pre-trained model on a new dataset.</field><field name="sentence">Previously, there was one purple-bordered box which showed themedians of the pixel distributions</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6668</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Training the pre-trained model on a new dataset.</field><field name="sentence">Now there are four purple-bordered boxes which show,in order, the mode, median, mean, and standard deviation</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6669</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Training the pre-trained model on a new dataset.</field><field name="sentence">There are now threeboxes with black borders, showing the same error visualization as before, butfor the mode and mean as well as the median</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6670</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Training the pre-trained model on a new dataset.</field><field name="sentence">The white-bordered boxes are a newkind of error visualization, in which colors on the grayline between black andwhite correspond to correct predictions, orange corresponds to a false positive,and blue corresponds to a false negative</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6671</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Training the pre-trained model on a new dataset.</field><field name="sentence">The final mango-bordered box is notinformative for this exercise.The pre-trained model hasn't seen the Condition E dataset, so we should expectits predictions to be poor</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6672</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Training the pre-trained model on a new dataset.</field><field name="sentence">Note, however, there is some transfer of the nuclearlabel even before training.You can find the input images, consisting of a *z*-stack of 26 images, here   Warning: 100 MB download .</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6673</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Training</field><field name="sentence">We can train the network on the Condition E data on a single machine using acommand like:By default, this uses the ADAM optimizer with a learning rate of 1e-If youwish to visualize training progress, you can run TensorBoard  on BASE_DIRECTORY:You should eventually see a training curve that looks like this:After 50,000 steps, which takes about a week on a 32-core machine, predictionson the eval data should have substantially improved.You can run this command to generate predictions:Note, we've dropped the restore_directory argument, so the model will run inference using the latest checkpoint it finds in BASE_DIRECTORY.Here's what the predictions should look like on the evaluation data:Note, there is a bug in the normalization of the DAPI_CONFOCAL channel causingit to have a reduced dynamic range in the ground-truth image</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6674</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Training</field><field name="sentence">Comparing theinitial nuclear predictions with these, it is clear the network learned to matchthe reduced dynamic range.For reference, here's what predictions should look like on the train data:Note, if we train too long the model will eventually overfit on the train dataand predictions will worsen</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6675</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Training</field><field name="sentence">This was not an issue in the paper, because therewe simultaneously trained on all tasks, so that each task regularized the</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6676</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Citing the code</field><field name="sentence">If you use this code, please cite our paper:Christiansen E, Yang S, Ando D, Javaherian A, Skibinski G, Lipnick S, Mount E, O'Neil A, Shah K, Lee A, Goyal P, Fedus W, Poplin R, Esteva A, Berndl M, Rubin L, Nelson P, Finkbeiner S</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6677</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Citing the code</field><field name="sentence">In silico labeling: Predicting fluorescent labels in unlabeled images</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6678</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Citing the code</field><field name="sentence">Cell</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6679</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Citing the code</field><field name="sentence">2018 Fix the tests</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6680</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Citing the code</field><field name="sentence">Fix the DAPI_CONFOCAL normalization bug for the Condition E data</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6681</field><field name="title">google-in-silico-labeling</field><field name="session">Citing the code</field><field name="sentence">Note: This bug was introduced after</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6682</field><field name="title">google-inception</field><field name="session">Inception</field><field name="sentence">This repository contains a reference pre-trained network for the Inceptionmodel, complementing the Google publication.Going Deeper with Convolutions, CVPR Christian Szegedy, Wei Liu, Yangqing Jia, Pierre Sermanet, Scott Reed,Dragomir Anguelov, Dumitru Erhan, Vincent Vanhoucke, Andrew Rabinovich.You can view "inception.ipynb" directly on GitHub, or clone therepository, install dependencies listed in the notebook and play with codeYou may also be interested in the  Multibox approach that uses the Inception architecture for object detection, alsoavailable on GitHub.Disclaimer: this is not an official Google product  experimental or otherwise .</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6683</field><field name="title">google-incremental-dom</field><field name="session">Overview</field><field name="sentence">Incremental DOM is a library for building up DOM trees and updating them in-place when data changes</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6684</field><field name="title">google-incremental-dom</field><field name="session">Overview</field><field name="sentence">It differs from the established virtual DOM approach in that no intermediate tree is created  the existing tree is mutated in-place</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6685</field><field name="title">google-incremental-dom</field><field name="session">Overview</field><field name="sentence">This approach significantly reduces memory allocation and GC thrashing for incremental updates to the DOM tree therefore increasing performance significantly in some cases.Incremental DOM is primarily intended as a compilation target for templating languages</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6686</field><field name="title">google-incremental-dom</field><field name="session">Overview</field><field name="sentence">It could be used to implement a higher level API for human consumption</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6687</field><field name="title">google-incremental-dom</field><field name="session">Overview</field><field name="sentence">The API was carefully designed to minimize heap allocations and where unavoidable ensure that as many objects as possible can be de-allocated by incremental GC</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6688</field><field name="title">google-incremental-dom</field><field name="session">Overview</field><field name="sentence">One unique feature of its API is that it separates opening and closing of tags so that it is suitable as a compilation target for templating languages that allow  temporarily  unbalanced HTML in templates  e.g</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6689</field><field name="title">google-incremental-dom</field><field name="session">Overview</field><field name="sentence">tags that are opened and closed in separate templates  and arbitrary logic for creating HTML attributes.*Think of it as ASM.dom.*</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6690</field><field name="title">google-incremental-dom</field><field name="session">Supported Browsers</field><field name="sentence">Incremental DOM supports IE9 and above.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6691</field><field name="title">google-incremental-dom</field><field name="session">Usage</field><field name="sentence">HTML is expressed in Incremental DOM using the elementOpen, elementClose, elementVoid and text methods</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6692</field><field name="title">google-incremental-dom</field><field name="session">Usage</field><field name="sentence">Consider the following example:var IncrementalDOM = require 'incremental-dom' ,function render data  {  elementVoid 'input', '',   'type', 'text'   ;  elementOpen 'div', '', null ;  elementClose 'div' ;To render or update an existing DOM node, the patch function is used:var patch = require 'incremental-dom' .patch;var data = {  text: 'Hello World!',  someCondition: truepatch myElement, function   {  render data ;} ;data.text = 'Hello World!';patch myElement, function   {  render data ;} ;</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6693</field><field name="title">google-incremental-dom</field><field name="session">Templating Languages and Libraries</field><field name="sentence">Check out  ECOSYSTEM.md   what others having been doing with Incremental DOM.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6694</field><field name="title">google-incremental-dom</field><field name="session">Via CDN</field><field name="sentence">To install the required development packages, run the following command:To run once:To build once:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6695</field><field name="title">google-indexable-pwa-samples</field><field name="session">Indexable PWA</field><field name="sentence">A sample ExpressJS PWA that explores and demonstrates the bestpractices for implementing a PWA in regards to indexability of content.Can be configured for 3 specific rendering modes:Install this package via npm:npm installInstall bower and the fetch polyfill to support Safari:npm install bowerbower install fetchRun the server via:node server.js</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6696</field><field name="title">google-indexable-pwa-samples</field><field name="session">Deploying to App Engine</field><field name="sentence">Follow this link to setup your App Engine project for Node.JS:gcloud app deploy app.yamlUse app.yaml to set environment variables to override the config.js file.Example .yaml file:runtime: nodejsvm: true  AMP_MODE: disabled  RENDER_MODE: hybrid  UPDATE_MODE: json</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6697</field><field name="title">google-indexable-pwa-samples</field><field name="session">Configuration Patterns</field><field name="sentence">Configure config.js:Recommended configuration patterns:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6698</field><field name="title">google-indexable-pwa-samples</field><field name="session">Server Sample</field><field name="sentence">For server-side rendering:{  "ampMode": "disabled",  "renderMode": "server",  "updateMode": "disabled",  "googleSiteVerificationToken": ""~~~~</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6699</field><field name="title">google-indexable-pwa-samples</field><field name="session">Client Sample</field><field name="sentence">For client-side rendering.updateMode can be configured as either 'json' or 'html'.{  "ampMode": "disabled",  "renderMode": "client",  "updateMode": "json",  "googleSiteVerificationToken": ""~~~~</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6700</field><field name="title">google-indexable-pwa-samples</field><field name="session">Hybrid Sample</field><field name="sentence">For hybrid rendering.updateMode can be configured as either 'json' or 'html'.{  "ampMode": "disabled",  "renderMode": "hybrid",  "updateMode": "json",  "googleSiteVerificationToken": ""~~~~</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6701</field><field name="title">google-indexed-db-as-promised</field><field name="session">indexed-db-as-promised</field><field name="sentence">! npm version  A thin wrapper around IndexedDB, making it much more pleasant to use byreturning Promise-likes</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6702</field><field name="title">google-indexed-db-as-promised</field><field name="session">indexed-db-as-promised</field><field name="sentence">Inspired by ideas in indexeddb-promised but written with the SyncPromise library to avoid issues with the transactionThis is not an official Google product.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6703</field><field name="title">google-indexed-db-as-promised</field><field name="session">Installation</field><field name="sentence">The APIs mirror native IndexedDB's, just returning a promise-like everywhereyou would want one.import indexedDBP from "indexed-db-as-promised";indexedDBP.open 'database', 1, {  upgrade db, { transaction, oldVersion, newVersion }  {  }} .then  db  => {  // Get the Jane's record  return db.transaction 'people' .run  tx  => {  } .then  record  => {  } .then  count  => {  } .then    => {  } ;} ;</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6704</field><field name="title">google-indexed-db-as-promised</field><field name="session">License</field><field name="sentence">Apache 2.0</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6705</field><field name="title">google-infact</field><field name="session">InFact: An easy way to construct C++ objects dynamically</field><field name="sentence">InFact provides an interpreter and factory for the construction ofinstances of C++ classes</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6706</field><field name="title">google-infact</field><field name="session">InFact: An easy way to construct C++ objects dynamically</field><field name="sentence">The syntax is very much like that of C++itself, and objects may be created that wrap other objects, just likein C++</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6707</field><field name="title">google-infact</field><field name="session">InFact: An easy way to construct C++ objects dynamically</field><field name="sentence">It supports all the common primitive types  string , as well as vectors of primitives or of Factory-constructibleobjects</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6708</field><field name="title">google-infact</field><field name="session">InFact: An easy way to construct C++ objects dynamically</field><field name="sentence">Here's what it looks like:// Construct a cow with a required argument, its name.Cow c1 = Cow name "Bessie"  ;// Construct a second cow with a different name, and an optional age.// Also, specifying a type is optional, since InFact does type inference.c2 = Cow name "Lani Moo" , age 2  ;// Construct a human pet owner with the two cows as pets.PetOwner p = HumanPetOwner pets {c1, c2}  ;Feeding the above to InFact’s Interpreter class will construct three new objects at run-time  the referents ofc1, c2 and p  _without any new C++ code_.While being very powerful, the library is also quite lightweight: itis a simple recursive-descent parser with a single token oflook-ahead, with the entire library implemented with fewer than 1000C++ statements</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6709</field><field name="title">google-infact</field><field name="session">InFact: An easy way to construct C++ objects dynamically</field><field name="sentence">The inspiration was the BeanShell library  for Java, whichprovides a very convenient mechanism for configuration of any Javaproject</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6710</field><field name="title">google-infact</field><field name="session">InFact: An easy way to construct C++ objects dynamically</field><field name="sentence">Similarly, InFact can be used as an effective configurationmechansim for C++ projects</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6711</field><field name="title">google-infact</field><field name="session">InFact: An easy way to construct C++ objects dynamically</field><field name="sentence">See the ReFr project  for an example, the default configuration file The interpreted InFact language supports _type inference_ and _namedparameters_</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6712</field><field name="title">google-infact</field><field name="session">InFact: An easy way to construct C++ objects dynamically</field><field name="sentence">Compile-time equivalents of these two properties areavailable with the Boost Parameter library.For documentation, please visit our documentation site</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6713</field><field name="title">google-infra-structured-map</field><field name="session">Usage</field><field name="sentence">Document your projects in a Markdown file:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6714</field><field name="title">google-infra-structured-map</field><field name="session">The Bigger Dig</field><field name="sentence">This is a multi-century project to build a subway from New York to LA.Next, define the geographic features of each project in KML:maintaining your map data</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6715</field><field name="title">google-infra-structured-map</field><field name="session">The Bigger Dig</field><field name="sentence">It exports KML and you can even pass your KMLdownload URL to the extract below.Next, build a JSON data file for powering your interactive map.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6716</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Inspector Spacetime  4e4c540d</field><field name="sentence">Motion specs are a necessary part of the engineering process</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6717</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Inspector Spacetime  4e4c540d</field><field name="sentence">It's often difficult and time consuming to deliver the data required to replicate motion on device</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6718</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Inspector Spacetime  4e4c540d</field><field name="sentence">With Inspector Spacetime you can generate this data along side the reference quicktime, with just one click.> This is not an official Google product</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6719</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Inspector Spacetime  4e4c540d</field><field name="sentence">Motion designers at Google just kinda like it a lot</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6720</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Inspector Spacetime  4e4c540d</field><field name="sentence">Built by  Adam Plouff  8638464d .</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6721</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">After Effects</field><field name="sentence">Close After EffectsDrag the InspectorSpacetime.jsx file into Applications > Adobe After Effects  version number  > Scripts > ScriptUI PanelsFire up After Effects againNavigate to the Window menu up top</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6722</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">After Effects</field><field name="sentence">At the bottom you'll see InspectorSpacetime.jsx</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6723</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Basics</field><field name="sentence">Select a pair or several pairs of keyframes and click the giant button</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6724</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Basics</field><field name="sentence">Your comp will be duplicated and resized to create space for all the useful spec data to live right alongside the reference animation.A new text layer is generated with all the selected element data</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6725</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Basics</field><field name="sentence">Raw text may be edited</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6726</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Basics</field><field name="sentence">Enabling the expression will update style and live values.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6727</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Live Text</field><field name="sentence">Spec data is based on the overall transition time</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6728</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Live Text</field><field name="sentence">Markers are placed at the time of the first and last selected keyframes as a reference for the transition time</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6729</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Live Text</field><field name="sentence">Moving the start and end markers updates:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6730</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Data output</field><field name="sentence">Keyframe data output:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6731</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Isolation Layer</field><field name="sentence">If your comp is really busy it can be tough to clearly see what's being spec'd</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6732</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Isolation Layer</field><field name="sentence">An isolation layer is just an adjustment layer that will grey out everything below it to get a little more focus on what you're showing.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6733</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Time Counter</field><field name="sentence">Created with every spec, a counter is also available as its own layer</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6734</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Time Counter</field><field name="sentence">Create a millisecond counter with a defined start and end point</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6735</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Time Counter</field><field name="sentence">Start the timer at the beginning of the transition to easily illustrate the global start time.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6736</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Pointer</field><field name="sentence">Everyone names things differently, which can lead to confusion</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6737</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Pointer</field><field name="sentence">So draw a line from spec data to the visual element and save yourself a lot of explaining</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6738</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Pointer</field><field name="sentence">This button will get you started, or just draw your own</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6739</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Pointer</field><field name="sentence">Either way, it'll make your life easier.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6740</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Why the dumb name?</field><field name="sentence">Named after the Doctor Who parody from the underrated NBC comedy  Community  a97544c1</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6741</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Why the dumb name?</field><field name="sentence">It was a really great show.In**spec**tor Spacetime</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6742</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Why the dumb name?</field><field name="sentence">It's a bad pun</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6743</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Why the dumb name?</field><field name="sentence">But I'm a dad</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6744</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">Why the dumb name?</field><field name="sentence">I can't help it.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6745</field><field name="title">google-inspectorspacetime</field><field name="session">License</field><field name="sentence">Apache 2.0</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6746</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Instant Hangouts</field><field name="sentence">**Disclaimer: due to Hangouts API changes, this app is no longer supported.**Instant Hangouts lets you easily add Google+ Hangouts to any web page:! default hangout  images/default_hangout.png  Google+ Hangout Button API  isrich but requires a bit of fiddling to get details right</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6747</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Instant Hangouts</field><field name="sentence">Instant Hangouts is athin wrapper that handles a bunch of the details for you:By default we display a Hangout name and information about the participants,rather than just a button to start a new Hangout.The Google API is loaded asynchronously to keep your pages fastConfiguration is very simple: just add attributes to your .</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6748</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">How it works</field><field name="sentence">You serve instanthangouts.0.1.0.js</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6749</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">How it works</field><field name="sentence">Then, you put the following HTML into yourpage where you want the Hangout to appear:only need our script once:We take care of loading the script asynchronously if possible so your pagesdon't wait until they've downloaded the Google API to render.Our Javascript looks at your page and finds all elements that haveclass='instanthangouts' on them</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6750</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">How it works</field><field name="sentence">We read the attributes of those tags tofigure out what arguments to pass to the Google API</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6751</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">How it works</field><field name="sentence">See below for the argumentsyou can put on these elements to configure your Hangouts.Next, we insert a new class='instanthangouts'</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6752</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">How it works</field><field name="sentence">We then call the Google API and pass in the argumentswe read from the element, rendering the Hangout</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6753</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">How it works</field><field name="sentence">This means you can have as manyHangout controls on a page as you want.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6754</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Modes</field><field name="sentence">We support two modes: *widget</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6755</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Widget</field><field name="sentence">Widget mode looks like this:! default hangout  images/default_hangout.png It is used by default, and can be explicitly selected by setting hangout in your HTML:end up in the same Hangout</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6756</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Widget</field><field name="sentence">Rooms are unique to the 3room_id, topic   see **Options*to values that will cause all Hangouts on a given page to have the same room,which is usually what users want.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6757</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Button</field><field name="sentence">Button mode looks like this:! button hangout  images/button_hangout.png It can be selected with the following HTML:allows some options  like creating a Hangout on Air  that the widget does notsupport</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6758</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Button</field><field name="sentence">See **Options*You can mix buttons and widgets on the same page.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6759</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Options</field><field name="sentence">We support the full Google+ Hangout Button API with the exception of adding Hangout apps to your page</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6760</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Options</field><field name="sentence">If you're using aHangout app, you probably want full control rather than going through an adapterlike Instant Hangouts.All options are set as HTML attributes on your tags</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6761</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Options</field><field name="sentence">All values are strings.The full list of options is:mode</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6762</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Options</field><field name="sentence">Ignored in widget mode</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6763</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Options</field><field name="sentence">See the official docs for possible values.only the value on the first  is honored.explicit, meaning no automatic processing is done and all renders must becalled via the API</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6764</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Options</field><field name="sentence">The other option is onload</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6765</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Options</field><field name="sentence">This does DOM traversal anddiscovery and is consequently slower</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6766</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Options</field><field name="sentence">parsetags is global, so only the valueon the first  is honored.default all Hangouts created with Instant Hangouts use the Instant Hangoutspublisher_id</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6767</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Options</field><field name="sentence">You can use your own if you want to be double sure that yourorganization's rooms won't overlap with another organization's  though bydefault we use the URL when constructing rooms, which in most cases will beunique to your organization .button mode</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6768</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Options</field><field name="sentence">Default is hangout</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6769</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Options</field><field name="sentence">No effect in button mode.the room_id is room_ plus the URL of the containing page</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6770</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Options</field><field name="sentence">No effect inbutton mode.value is presented to users in the Hangouts UI telling them what the Hangout isabout</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6771</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Options</field><field name="sentence">Default is Instant Hangout</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6772</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Options</field><field name="sentence">No effect in button mode.Default is 136.Default is 300.Here is a full example for the HTML you need in widget mode to set all customThis section covers development of Instant Hangouts</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6773</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Options</field><field name="sentence">You don't need to read itunless you want to contribute to the project.We use  npm  for package management and Node.js  for a development server</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6774</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Options</field><field name="sentence">You should install Node,which comes with npm, in whatever way is best on your system.Pull down the repo and install dependencies into ./node_modules withlocalhost during development because the URL is used when constructing rooms</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6775</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Options</field><field name="sentence">Ifyou use a hostname, you can bring up the test server on multiple machines andlog in with multiple accounts to do a real end-to-end test of the HangoutWe use  Grunt  to produce two files:generate new versions of these files</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6776</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Options</field><field name="sentence">You will also want to update the scripttags in this document.When developing, runtime there is a change</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6777</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Options</field><field name="sentence">This assumes you have installed grunt-cli globally,which is fairly common</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6778</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Options</field><field name="sentence">If you want to use the local version managed by InstantHangouts, instead runrunner</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6779</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Options</field><field name="sentence">To start:be run in that Chrome window</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6780</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Options</field><field name="sentence">Karma has its own file watcher and reruns testswhen either the source, tests, or index.html changes</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6781</field><field name="title">google-instant-hangouts</field><field name="session">Options</field><field name="sentence">We use Jasmine  for our test framework.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6782</field><field name="title">google-intelligent_annotation_dialogs</field><field name="session">Source code for Intelligent Annotation Dialogs</field><field name="sentence">This repository contains the source code which is used to run the experiments inour ArXiv paper:The code contains third party code  np_box_ops.py  from the  Tensorflow ObjectAPI</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6783</field><field name="title">google-intelligent_annotation_dialogs</field><field name="session">Disclaimer</field><field name="sentence">This is not an officially supported Google product.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6784</field><field name="title">google-intellij-cmdline-vcs-plugin</field><field name="session">Command-line "VCS" plugin for IntelliJ IDEA</field><field name="sentence">Makes calls to shell scripts to get all VCS-related job done.This allows you to write scripts to acoomodate even the strangiestVCS workflows you may encounter.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6785</field><field name="title">google-intellij-cmdline-vcs-plugin</field><field name="session">Command line script</field><field name="sentence">Should be placed into "/usr/local/bin/cmdline-vcs" and be executable.List of commands called from IntelliJ:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6786</field><field name="title">google-inverting-proxy</field><field name="session">Inverting Proxy and Agent</field><field name="sentence">This repository defines a reverse proxy that inverts the direction of trafficbetween the proxy and the backend servers.That design makes configuring and hosting backends much simpler than whatis required for traditional reverse proxies:The communication channel between the proxy and backends can be securedThe backends do not need to be exposed to incoming requests from the proxy.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6787</field><field name="title">google-inverting-proxy</field><field name="session">Disclaimer</field><field name="sentence">This is not an official Google product</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6788</field><field name="title">google-inverting-proxy</field><field name="session">Background</field><field name="sentence">A  reverse proxy  is a server thatforwards requests to one or more backend servers.Traditionally, this has been done by configuring the reverse proxy with theaddress of each backend, and then having it send a request to a backend foreach request it receives from a client.That meant each backend had to be able to receive incoming requests from theproxy</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6789</field><field name="title">google-inverting-proxy</field><field name="session">Background</field><field name="sentence">This implied one of two choices.Place the backend servers on a private network shared with the proxy.Place the backend servers on the public internet.The first choice requires the proxy and backends to be controlled by the samehosting provider, while the second requires the backends handle all of thesame overhead required for any internet hosting  SSL termination, protectionagainst DDoS attacks, etc .This project aims to limit the overhead of hosting a public server to justthe proxy while still allowing anyone to run a backend.The details of how this is accomplished are outlined below.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6790</field><field name="title">google-inverting-proxy</field><field name="session">Design</field><field name="sentence">This project defines two components:Something that we are calling the "Inverting Proxy"An agent that runs alongside a backend and forwards requests to itThe inverting proxy can be run on App Engine</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6791</field><field name="title">google-inverting-proxy</field><field name="session">Design</field><field name="sentence">It requires incoming requests beauthenticated via the  Users API and forwards those requests to the appropriate backend, via the agent.Since neither the backend nor the agent will be accessible from the publicinternet, requests are not directly forwarded to the backend</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6792</field><field name="title">google-inverting-proxy</field><field name="session">Design</field><field name="sentence">Instead,the direction of that traffic is inverted</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6793</field><field name="title">google-inverting-proxy</field><field name="session">Design</field><field name="sentence">The agent sends a request to theinverting proxy, the proxy waits for incoming client requests, andthen the proxy responds to the request from the agent with those clientrequests in the response body.The agent then forwards those requests to the backend, takes the responsesthat it gets back, and sends them as a request to the inverting proxy.Finally, the inverting proxy extracts the backend's response from theagent's request and sends it as the response to the original clientAn example request flow looks like this:The important thing to note is that the request from the client  #2  matchesthe request to the backend  #4  and the response from the backend  #5  matchesthe response to the client  #7 .</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6794</field><field name="title">google-inverting-proxy</field><field name="session">Components</field><field name="sentence">There are two components required for the inverting proxy to work:The proxy itself, which must be accessible from the public internet.The forwarding agent, which must be able to forward requests to the backend.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6795</field><field name="title">google-inverting-proxy</field><field name="session">Inverting Proxy</field><field name="sentence">The inverting proxy serves the same roll as a reverse proxy, but additionallyinverts the direction of traffic to the agent.We implement the inverting proxy as an App Engine app</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6796</field><field name="title">google-inverting-proxy</field><field name="session">Inverting Proxy</field><field name="sentence">The app is written inGo and its source code is under the 'app' subdirectory.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6797</field><field name="title">google-inverting-proxy</field><field name="session">Forwarding Agent</field><field name="sentence">The agent receives the inverted traffic from the proxy and inverts it againbefore forwarding it to the backend</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6798</field><field name="title">google-inverting-proxy</field><field name="session">Forwarding Agent</field><field name="sentence">This ensures that the requests from theclient match the requests to the backend and that the responses from thebackend match the responses to the client.The forwarding agent is standalone binary written in Go and its source codeis under the 'agent' subdirectory.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6799</field><field name="title">google-inverting-proxy</field><field name="session">Prerequisites</field><field name="sentence">First,  create a Google Cloud Platform project that will host your proxy, and ensure that you have the Google Cloud SDK  installed on your machine.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6800</field><field name="title">google-inverting-proxy</field><field name="session">Setup</field><field name="sentence">Save the ID of your project in the environment variable PROJECT_ID, and thenrun the commandone for agents to contact, and one that implements an API for managingproxy endpoints .</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6801</field><field name="title">google-inverting-proxy</field><field name="session">Registering Backends</field><field name="sentence">Before you can connect a backend server to your proxy, you must use the proxy'sadmin API to create a record of that backend</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6802</field><field name="title">google-inverting-proxy</field><field name="session">Registering Backends</field><field name="sentence">This is just a simple HTTPREST API with create, list, and delete operations</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6803</field><field name="title">google-inverting-proxy</field><field name="session">Registering Backends</field><field name="sentence">There is no client toolprovided for the admin API, but you can access it using curl.To list the current backends:  Alternatively, you can use the special string "allUsers" to make your server public</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6804</field><field name="title">google-inverting-proxy</field><field name="session">Registering Backends</field><field name="sentence">on the machine where the agent runs.Finally, to delete a backend:Once you have created the record for your backend using the API, you canrun the agent alongside your server with the following command:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6805</field><field name="title">google-inverting-proxy</field><field name="session">Limitations</field><field name="sentence">Currently, the inverting proxy only supports HTTP requests</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6806</field><field name="title">google-inverting-proxy</field><field name="session">Limitations</field><field name="sentence">In particular,websockets are not supported, so you have to use an adapter like socket.ioif you want to use the inverting proxy with a service that requires websockets.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6807</field><field name="title">google-ion</field><field name="session">Ion</field><field name="sentence">Ion is a portable suite of libraries and tools for building client applications,especially graphical ones</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6808</field><field name="title">google-ion</field><field name="session">Ion</field><field name="sentence">It is small, fast, robust, and is cross-platformacross many platforms and devices, including desktops, mobile devices, browsers,and other embedded platforms.For more details and a fair amount of documentation see</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6809</field><field name="title">google-ion</field><field name="session">Why Use Ion?</field><field name="sentence">NOTE: This is not an official Google product.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6810</field><field name="title">google-ios-chatbot</field><field name="session">Chatbot with API.AI and Google Cloud APIs</field><field name="sentence">This sample demonstrates how to build an iOS chatbot with Google Cloud Vision,Speech, and Translate APIs and API.AI</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6811</field><field name="title">google-ios-chatbot</field><field name="session">Chatbot with API.AI and Google Cloud APIs</field><field name="sentence">! English Demo   ! The Google Assistant / Google Home Demo</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6812</field><field name="title">google-ios-chatbot</field><field name="session">Prerequisites</field><field name="sentence">Create a new project on Enable Billing.Go to API Manager.Go to CredentialsCreate credentials</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6813</field><field name="title">google-ios-chatbot</field><field name="session">Prerequisites</field><field name="sentence">Choose API Key.Replace @"your google API key" with your google API key in  CBDefines.m  ChatBot/ChatBot/Helpers/CBDefines.m</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6814</field><field name="title">google-ios-chatbot</field><field name="session">API.AI</field><field name="sentence">Optionally, follow these steps to create your own API.AI agents.Create TourGuide agent.Go to Settings and import  api.ai/TourGuide.zip  api.ai/TourGuide.zip</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6815</field><field name="title">google-ios-chatbot</field><field name="session">API.AI</field><field name="sentence">Optional steps to support Chinese  Create TourGuideChinese agent withlanguage set to Chinese.Go to Settings and import  api.ai/TourGuideChinese.zip  api.ai/TourGuideChinese.zip Replace CBApiAiToken with your API.AI token in  CBDefines.m  ChatBot/ChatBot/Helpers/CBDefines.m</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6816</field><field name="title">google-ios-chatbot</field><field name="session">API.AI</field><field name="sentence">You can find your token from the API.AI agent setting page.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6817</field><field name="title">google-ios-chatbot</field><field name="session">Chinese Demo</field><field name="sentence">! Chinese Demo</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6818</field><field name="title">google-ios-chatbot</field><field name="session">License</field><field name="sentence">This sample is released under the  Apache 2.0 license  LICENSE .</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6819</field><field name="title">google-ios-chatbot</field><field name="session">Disclaimer</field><field name="sentence">This is not an official Google product.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6820</field><field name="title">google-ios-chatbot</field><field name="session">Authors</field><field name="sentence">Chang Luo  changluo  and  Bob Liu  bobliu  getting-started :  cloud-console :  git :  xcode :  billing :  enable-speech :  api-key :  cocoapods :  changluo :  bobliu :  google-home :</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6821</field><field name="title">google-ios-device-control</field><field name="session">iOS Device Control Library</field><field name="sentence">iOS Device Control is a Java library for controlling the iOS Simulator and real physical  iOS devices tethered to a device running macOS</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6822</field><field name="title">google-ios-device-control</field><field name="session">iOS Device Control Library</field><field name="sentence">The library offersthe ability to get device properties, install and start applications, takescreenshots, capture logs, and more!Examples of how to use this library can be found here  src/com/google/iosdevicecontrol/examples</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6823</field><field name="title">google-ios-device-control</field><field name="session">iOS Device Control Library</field><field name="sentence">To build the examples, run:which will create two runnable jars in the target directory.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6824</field><field name="title">google-ios-device-control</field><field name="session">Installation</field><field name="sentence">iOS Device Control only works on macOS with tethered real devices or with Xcode8+ with the simctl tool installed for the iOS Simulator.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6825</field><field name="title">google-ios-device-control</field><field name="session">Simulator Automation</field><field name="sentence">Install  Xcode 8 or above and verify the following command works:The following dependencies can be installed easily with homebrew Install libusbmuxd by building from source:Install libimobiledevice by building from source:Install ideviceinstaller by building from source:Install idevice_app_runner and idevicewebinspectorproxy by building fromsource</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6826</field><field name="title">google-ios-device-control</field><field name="session">Simulator Automation</field><field name="sentence">This can be done by following the instructions outlined in theREADMEs of the respective projects in the  third_party directory  third_party .</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6827</field><field name="title">google-ios-device-control</field><field name="session">Optional Utilities</field><field name="sentence">Most of the iOS Device Control library can be used with just the above tools.For additional control of real devices, the following tools can optionally beInstall  Apple Configurator 2 and install the automation tools by selecting the "Install Automation Tools..."option under the Apple Configurator 2 menu.Install the provided OpenUrl app by following the instructions here  OpenUrlApp/README  to automate Safari on real devices.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6828</field><field name="title">google-ios-device-control</field><field name="session">Troubleshooting</field><field name="sentence">For real devices, make sure that both the device is trusted and the lockdownfolder has the correct permissions.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6829</field><field name="title">google-ios-device-control</field><field name="session">License</field><field name="sentence">iOS Device Control is licensed under the open-source Apache 2.0 license  LICENSE .</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6830</field><field name="title">google-ios-device-control</field><field name="session">Contributing</field><field name="sentence">Please  see the guidelines for contributing  CONTRIBUTING.md  before creatingpull requests.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6831</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">iOS WebKit Debug Proxy</field><field name="sentence">The ios_webkit_debug_proxy  aka _iwdp_  proxies requests from usbmuxd daemon over a websocket connection, allowing developers to send commands to MobileSafari and UIWebViews on real and simulated iOS devices.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6832</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">Installation</field><field name="sentence">iOS WebKit Debug Proxy works on Linux, MacOS & Windows.On a MacOS, it's easiest to install with  homebrew On Linux  or MacOS :sudo apt-get install autoconf automake libusb-dev libusb-1.0-0-dev libplist-dev libplist++-dev usbmuxd libtool libimobiledevice-devgit clone cd ios-webkit-debug-proxymakesudo make install</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6833</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">Usage</field><field name="sentence">On Linux, you must run the usbmuxd daemon</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6834</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">Usage</field><field name="sentence">The above install adds a /lib/udev rule to start the daemon whenever a device is attached</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6835</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">Usage</field><field name="sentence">To verify that usbmuxd can list your attached device s , run idevice_id -l</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6836</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">Start the simulator or device</field><field name="sentence">The iOS Simulator is supported, but it must be started **before*Your attached iOS devices must have ≥1 open browser tabs and the inspector enabled via:  Settings > Safari > Advanced > Web Inspector = ON</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6837</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">Start the proxy</field><field name="sentence">ios_webkit_debug_proxy can be used with many tools such as Chrome DevTools and Safari Web Inspector.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6838</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">Chrome Devtools</field><field name="sentence">To use Chrome DevTools it's the recommendation to use the  RemoteDebug/remotedebug-ios-webkit-adapter  project, which has instructions on how to setup Chrome to remote debug iOS devices, much similar to Android debugging.The reason is that recent versions of Chrome and Safari there're major discrepancies between  Chrome Remote Debugging Protocol  and Apple's  Remote Web Inspector service  which means that newer versions of Chrome DevTools aren't compatible with Safari.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6839</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">Safari Web Inspector</field><field name="sentence">You can use Safari Web Inspector extracted from Webkit sources, e.g</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6840</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">Safari Web Inspector</field><field name="sentence">artygus/webkit-webinspector</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6841</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">Firefox DevTools via Valence</field><field name="sentence">Another option is  mozilla/valence  which enables Firefox DevTools to be used with iOS.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6842</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">View and inspect debuggable tabs</field><field name="sentence">Navigate to  localhost:9221  You'll see a listing of all connected devices.Click through to view tabs available on each, and click through again to open the DevTools for a tab.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6843</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">Setting the DevTools UI URL</field><field name="sentence">Chrome DevTools UI  used as a default frontend: Chromium checkout  or another URL:Just the same, you can apply the appropriate port  9222  and page  2  values below.The -f value must end in ".html"</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6844</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">Setting the DevTools UI URL</field><field name="sentence">Due to security reasons, https URLs will not work; use http or force-allow with the URL bar's shield icon</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6845</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">Setting the DevTools UI URL</field><field name="sentence">As of Chrome 45, the primary URL  changed  from devtools.html to inspector.html.To disable the frontend proxy, use the --no-frontend argument.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6846</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">Port assigment</field><field name="sentence">The default configuration works well for most developers</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6847</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">Port assigment</field><field name="sentence">The device_id-to-port assignment defaults to:If a port is in use then the next available port will be used, up to the range limit.The port assignment is first-come-first-serve but is preserved if a device is detached and reattached, assuming that the proxy is not restarted, e.g.:  the device list gets :9221  attach A gets :9222  attach B gets :9223  detach A, doesn't affect B's port  attach C gets :9224  not :9222   reattach A gets :9222 again  not :9225 The port assignment rules can be set via the command line with -c</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6848</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">Port assigment</field><field name="sentence">The default is equivalent to:where "null" represents the device list</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6849</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">Port assigment</field><field name="sentence">The following example restricts the proxy to a single device and port:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6850</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">undefined reference to symbol 'log10@@GLIBC_2.2.5'</field><field name="sentence">Run this before make: ./configure LIBS="-lm"</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6851</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">error while loading shared libraries: libimobiledevice.so.6</field><field name="sentence">Run sudo ldconfig</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6852</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">idevice_id not found</field><field name="sentence">The idevice_id executable may be found as part of the libimobiledevice-utils package.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6853</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">could not start com.apple.webinspector! success</field><field name="sentence">Remove and rebuild libimobiledevice</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6854</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">Could not connect to lockdownd  or doesn't work with iOS10+</field><field name="sentence">> Could not connect to lockdownd</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6855</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">Could not connect to lockdownd  or doesn't work with iOS10+</field><field name="sentence">Exiting.: No such file or directory</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6856</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">Could not connect to lockdownd  or doesn't work with iOS10+</field><field name="sentence">Unable to attach  inspector ios_webkit_debug_proxyCheck the device for  a prompt to trust the connected computer  Choose "Trust" and try again.> Could not connect to lockdownd</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6857</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">Could not connect to lockdownd  or doesn't work with iOS10+</field><field name="sentence">Exiting.: Broken pipe</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6858</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">Could not connect to lockdownd  or doesn't work with iOS10+</field><field name="sentence">Unable to attach  inspectorPlease upgrade libimobiledevice to version from master and rebuild ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6859</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">Could not connect to lockdownd  or doesn't work with iOS10+</field><field name="sentence">Upcoming 1.2.1 has many fixes but not marked for release just yet</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6860</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">Could not connect to lockdownd  or doesn't work with iOS10+</field><field name="sentence">If you're on OS X:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6861</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">iOS 11</field><field name="sentence">> Could not connect to lockdown</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6862</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">iOS 11</field><field name="sentence">Exiting.: Resource temporarily unavailable> Unable to connect to XXX  > Please verify that Settings > Safari > Advanced > Web Inspector = ONBuild from master brew reinstall --HEAD ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6863</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">Can not see Simulator</field><field name="sentence">Lastly, always try replugging in the USB cable.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6864</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">IWDP Clients</field><field name="sentence">JSON-formatted APIs are provided for programmatic clients.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6865</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">Design</field><field name="sentence">! Alt overview  overview.png "Overview" View the  design document  design.md  for an overview of the source layout and architecture.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6866</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">License and Copyright</field><field name="sentence">Google BSD license <>Copyright 2012 Google Inc</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6867</field><field name="title">google-ios-webkit-debug-proxy</field><field name="session">License and Copyright</field><field name="sentence">The proxy uses the following open-source packages:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6868</field><field name="title">google-iosched-ios</field><field name="session">Google I/O iOS App</field><field name="sentence">Google I/O is a developer conference held each year with two days of deeptechnical content featuring technical sessions and hundreds of demonstrationsfrom developers showcasing their technologies.This project is the iOS app for the conference.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6869</field><field name="title">google-iosched-ios</field><field name="session">Building</field><field name="sentence">You'll need a Firebase project to run IOsched</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6870</field><field name="title">google-iosched-ios</field><field name="session">Building</field><field name="sentence">Copy your project'sGoogleService-Info.plist file into the Source/IOsched/Configurationdirectory</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6871</field><field name="title">google-iosched-ios</field><field name="session">Building</field><field name="sentence">For instructions on how to create an iOS app in your Firebaseproject, see the "Add Firebase to your app" section of this document CocoaPods 1.4.0 and Xcode 9.2 or higher are required.Run pod install in the Source directory, open IOsched.xcworkspace, andbuild and run the IOsched target.Note that the backend is dependent on Cloud Functions and Firestore, sowhen running the app you may not see any data if your project's Firestoredata store is empty</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6872</field><field name="title">google-iosched-ios</field><field name="session">Building</field><field name="sentence">Similarly, backend functions like reservationsand stars won't function.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6873</field><field name="title">google-iosched</field><field name="session">Features</field><field name="sentence">The app displays a list of conference events reviews, codelabs, etc</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6874</field><field name="title">google-iosched</field><field name="session">Features</field><field name="sentence">types and by topics  Android, Firebase, etc</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6875</field><field name="title">google-iosched</field><field name="session">Features</field><field name="sentence">Users can see details aboutevents, and they can star events that interest them</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6876</field><field name="title">google-iosched</field><field name="session">Features</field><field name="sentence">Conference attendees canreserve events to guarantee a seat.The app also displays a map of the venue and shows informational pages to guideattendees during the conference</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6877</field><field name="title">google-iosched</field><field name="session">Features</field><field name="sentence"></field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6878</field><field name="title">google-iosched</field><field name="session">Development Environment</field><field name="sentence">The app is written entirely in Kotlin and uses the Gradle build system.To build the app, use the gradlew build command or use "Import Project" inAndroid Studio</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6879</field><field name="title">google-iosched</field><field name="session">Development Environment</field><field name="sentence">A canary or stable version >= 3.2 of Android Studio isrequired and may be downloaded here</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6880</field><field name="title">google-iosched</field><field name="session">Architecture</field><field name="sentence">The 2018 version of the app constitutes a comprehensive rewrite</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6881</field><field name="title">google-iosched</field><field name="session">Architecture</field><field name="sentence">Thearchitecture is built around Android Architecture Components We followed the recommendations laid out in the Guide to App Architecture when deciding on the architecture for the app</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6882</field><field name="title">google-iosched</field><field name="session">Architecture</field><field name="sentence">We kept logic away fromActivities and Fragments and moved it to ViewModel We observed data using LiveData and used the  Data Binding Library to bind UI components in layouts to the app's data sources.We used a Repository layer for handling data operations</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6883</field><field name="title">google-iosched</field><field name="session">Architecture</field><field name="sentence">IOSched's data comesfrom a few different sources  Cloud Firestore  either remotely or ina local cache for offline use , user preferences and settings are stored inSharedPreferences, conference data is stored remotely and is fetched and storedin memory for the app to use, etc</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6884</field><field name="title">google-iosched</field><field name="session">Architecture</field><field name="sentence">are responsible for handling all data operations and abstracting the data sourcesfrom the rest of the app  we liked using Firestore, but if we wanted to swap itout for a different data source in the future, our architecture allows us to doso in a clean way .We implemented a lightweight domain layer, which sits between the data layerand the presentation layer, and handles discrete pieces of business logic offthe UI thread</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6885</field><field name="title">google-iosched</field><field name="session">Architecture</field><field name="sentence">See the .\*UseCase.kt files under shared/domain for examples We used  Dagger2  for dependency injectionand we heavily relied on dagger-android  to abstract awayboiler-plate code.We used  Espresso for basic instrumentation tests and JUnit and Mockito  for unit testing.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6886</field><field name="title">google-iosched</field><field name="session">Firebase</field><field name="sentence">The app makes considerable use of the following Firebase components:for all user data  events starred or reserved by a user</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6887</field><field name="title">google-iosched</field><field name="session">Firebase</field><field name="sentence">Firestore gave usautomatic sync  and also seamlessly managed offline functionalityfor us.allowed us to run backend code</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6888</field><field name="title">google-iosched</field><field name="session">Firebase</field><field name="sentence">The reservations feature heavily depended on CloudFunctions working in conjuction with Firestore.let us inform the app about changes to conference data on our server.manage in-app constants.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6889</field><field name="title">google-iosched</field><field name="session">Kotlin</field><field name="sentence">We made an early decision to rewrite the app from scratch to bring it in linewith our thinking about modern Android architecture</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6890</field><field name="title">google-iosched</field><field name="session">Kotlin</field><field name="sentence">Using Kotlin for therewrite was an easy choice: we liked Kotlin's expressive, concise, andpowerful syntax; we found that Kotlin's support for safety features fornullability and immutability made our code more resilient; and we leveraged theenhanced functionality provided by Android Ktx extensions</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6891</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2015</field><field name="session">Setup</field><field name="sentence">to run and deploy GAE-based backend  hint: gcloud components update app</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6892</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2015</field><field name="session">Setup</field><field name="sentence">configuration by executing the following command: gcloud config set project</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6893</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2015</field><field name="session">Setup</field><field name="sentence">Project ID can be any non-empty string if you just want to run the app locally.gulp setupIf you plan on modifying source code, be a good citizen and:Install  EditorConfig plugin  for your favourite browser.Obey the pre-commit hook that's installed as part of gulp setup.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6894</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2015</field><field name="session">Running</field><field name="sentence">Run gulp serve to start a standalone backend, while still enjoying live-reload.You'll need Go for that.Normally the app is running in "dev" environment but you can change thatby providing --env argument to the gulp task:  # run in dev mode, default:  gulp serve  # set app environment to production:  gulp serve --env prod  # or run as if we were in staging:  gulp serve --env stage  Not that this does not change the way the backend code is compiledor the front-end is built</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6895</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2015</field><field name="session">Running</field><field name="sentence">It merely changes a variable values,which the app takes into account when rendering a page or responding to a request.Running in stage or prod requires real credentials when accessing external services.You'll need to run a one-off gulp decrypt which will decrypt a service account private key.You can also use GAE dev appserver by running gulp serve:gae</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6896</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2015</field><field name="session">Running</field><field name="sentence">This is closer to whatwe're using in our webapp environment but a bit slower on startup.You'll need gcloud tool and app component to do this.To change the app environment when using GAE SDK, provide --env argument:  # run in dev mode, default:  gulp serve:gae  # set app environment to production:  gulp serve:gae --env prod  # or run as if we were in staging:  gulp serve:gae --env stage  Other arguments are:Run gulp</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6897</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2015</field><field name="session">Running</field><field name="sentence">This will create dist directory with both front-end and backend parts, ready for deploy.**Note**: Build won't succeed if either gulp jshint or gulp jscs reports errors.You can also serve the build from dist by running gulp serve:dist,and navigating to serve:dist runs the app in prod mode by default</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6898</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2015</field><field name="session">Running</field><field name="sentence">You can change thatby providing the --env argument as with other serve tasks</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6899</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2015</field><field name="session">Running</field><field name="sentence">For instance:  # run in stage instead of prod  gulp serve:dist --env stage</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6900</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2015</field><field name="session">Deploying</field><field name="sentence">To deploy complete application on App Engine:Run gulp which will build both frontend and backend in dist directory.Run gcloud preview app deploy dist/backend --version .The app will be deployed to the project configured in gcloud tool.To check which project you're deploying to, run gcloud config listand look for project = ..</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6901</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2015</field><field name="session">Deploying</field><field name="sentence">line.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6902</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2015</field><field name="session">Backend</field><field name="sentence">Backend is written in Go</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6903</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2015</field><field name="session">Backend</field><field name="sentence">It can run on either Google App Engine or any other platform as a standalonebinary program.gulp backend will build a self-sufficient backend server and place the binary in backend/bin/server.gulp backend:test will run backend server tests</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6904</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2015</field><field name="session">Backend</field><field name="sentence">If, while working on the backend, you feel tiredof running the command again and again, use gulp backend:test --watch to watch for file changesand re-run tests automatically.Add --gae cmd line argument to the test task to run GAE-based tests.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6905</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2015</field><field name="session">Debugging</field><field name="sentence">A list of tools to help in a debugging process.**NOT available in prod**</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6906</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2015</field><field name="session">Proxy with the service account credentials</field><field name="sentence">status code, content-type header and the content.Useful for browsing original CMS data on staging GCS bucket: go/iowastaging/debug/srvget?url=</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6907</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2015</field><field name="session">Send GCM push notifications</field><field name="sentence">Follow instructions on that page.On staging server this is  go/iowastaging/debug/push</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6908</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2015</field><field name="session">Re-sync local datastore with remote</field><field name="sentence">Frontend tests are run via Configuration is in wct.conf.js.To run tests, install wct globally:and run:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6909</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2016</field><field name="session">Setup</field><field name="sentence">correctly by running goapp version, which should output something like  go version go1.6  appengine-1.9.35 .npm installIf you plan on modifying source code, be a good citizen and:Install  EditorConfig plugin  for your favourite editor.Obey the pre-commit hook that's installed as part of gulp setup.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6910</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2016</field><field name="session">Running</field><field name="sentence">Run gulp serve to start the app.Normally the app is running in "dev" environment but you can change thatby providing --env argument to the gulp task:  # run in dev mode, default:  gulp serve  # set app environment to production:  gulp serve --env prod  # or run as if we were in staging:  gulp serve --env stage  Not that this does not change the way the backend code is compiledor the front-end is built</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6911</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2016</field><field name="session">Running</field><field name="sentence">It merely changes a "environment" variable value,which the app takes into account when rendering a page or responding to a request.Running in stage or prod requires real credentials when accessing external services.You'll need to run a one-off gulp decrypt which will decrypt a service account private key.Other arguments are:Run gulp</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6912</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2016</field><field name="session">Running</field><field name="sentence">This will create dist directory with both front-end and backend parts, ready for deploy.**Note**: Build won't succeed if either gulp jshint or gulp jscs reports errors.You can also serve the build from dist by running gulp serve:dist,and navigating to serve:dist runs the app in prod mode by default</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6913</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2016</field><field name="session">Running</field><field name="sentence">You can change thatby providing the --env argument as with other serve tasks</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6914</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2016</field><field name="session">Running</field><field name="sentence">For instance:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6915</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2016</field><field name="session">Deploying</field><field name="sentence">To deploy complete application on App Engine:Run gulp serve:dist which will build the app in dist directoryPerform any necessary manual checks.Run GAE_SDK/goapp deploy -application io-webapp-2016 -version  dist/backend/.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6916</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2016</field><field name="session">Backend</field><field name="sentence">Backend is written in Go, hosted on Google App Engine.cd backend && goapp test will run backend server tests</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6917</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2016</field><field name="session">Backend</field><field name="sentence">You'll need to make surethere's a server.config file in the backend dir.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6918</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2016</field><field name="session">Debugging</field><field name="sentence">A list of tools to help in a debugging process.**NOT available in prod**</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6919</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2016</field><field name="session">Proxy with the service account credentials</field><field name="sentence">status code, content-type header and the content.Useful for browsing original CMS data on staging GCS bucket: go/iowastaging/debug/srvget?url=</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6920</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2016</field><field name="session">Creating Databases/Shards and setting them up</field><field name="sentence">When setting up your own version of the Google IO Web app you need to create new Firebase databases,set them up and configure the app to use them.First, create one or more  depending on how many shards you need  Firebase databases from and note their Databases URLs.In the backend/server.config file list the Firebase Databases URLs in the firebase.shards attribute.For each Firebase databases you need to configure configure Login and Auth:Run the following command to deploy the Firebase Security rules to all shards:By default the above will deploy rules to the dev Firebase shards.To deploy the rules to other environments' shards run:Follow instructions on that page.On staging server this is  go/iowastaging/debug/push</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6921</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2016</field><field name="session">Re-sync local datastore with remote</field><field name="sentence">Frontend tests are run via Configuration is in wct.conf.js.To run tests, install wct globally:and run:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6922</field><field name="title">google-ioweb2016</field><field name="session">License</field><field name="sentence">Apache 2.0  © 2016 Google Inc.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6923</field><field name="title">google-j2objc</field><field name="session">J2ObjC: Java to Objective-C Translator and Runtime #</field><field name="sentence">**Project site:***J2ObjC blog:***Questions and discussion:*</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6924</field><field name="title">google-j2objc</field><field name="session">What J2ObjC Is ###</field><field name="sentence">J2ObjC is an open-source command-line tool from Google that translatesJava source code to Objective-C for the iOS  iPhone/iPad  platform</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6925</field><field name="title">google-j2objc</field><field name="session">What J2ObjC Is ###</field><field name="sentence">This toolenables Java source to be part of an iOS application's build, as no editingof the generated files is necessary</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6926</field><field name="title">google-j2objc</field><field name="session">What J2ObjC Is ###</field><field name="sentence">The goal is to write an app's non-UIcode  such as application logic and data models  in Java, which is thenshared by web apps  using  GWT  Android apps,and iOS apps.J2ObjC supports most Java language and runtime features required byclient-side application developers, including exceptions, inner andanonymous classes, generic types, threads and reflection</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6927</field><field name="title">google-j2objc</field><field name="session">What J2ObjC Is ###</field><field name="sentence">JUnit testtranslation and execution is also supported.J2ObjC is currently beta quality</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6928</field><field name="title">google-j2objc</field><field name="session">What J2ObjC Is ###</field><field name="sentence">Several Google projects rely on it, butwhen new projects first start working with it, they usually find new bugsto be fixed</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6929</field><field name="title">google-j2objc</field><field name="session">What J2ObjC Is ###</field><field name="sentence">If you run into issues with your project, please report them!</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6930</field><field name="title">google-j2objc</field><field name="session">What J2ObjC isn't ###</field><field name="sentence">J2ObjC does not provide any sort of platform-independent UI toolkit, nor arethere any plans to do so in the future</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6931</field><field name="title">google-j2objc</field><field name="session">What J2ObjC isn't ###</field><field name="sentence">We believe that iOS UI code needs tobe written in Objective-C, Objective-C++ or Swift using Apple's iOS SDK  AndroidUIs using Android's API, web app UIs using GWT, etc</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6932</field><field name="title">google-j2objc</field><field name="session">What J2ObjC isn't ###</field><field name="sentence">.J2ObjC cannot convert Android binary applications</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6933</field><field name="title">google-j2objc</field><field name="session">What J2ObjC isn't ###</field><field name="sentence">Developers must have sourcecode for their Android app, which they either own or are licensed to use.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6934</field><field name="title">google-j2objc</field><field name="session">Requirements ##</field><field name="sentence">This library is distributed under the Apache 2.0 license found in the LICENSE  file.The protocol buffers library is distributed under the same BSD license asGoogle's protocol buffers</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6935</field><field name="title">google-j2objc</field><field name="session">Requirements ##</field><field name="sentence">See its README  and LICENSE</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6936</field><field name="title">google-jacs</field><field name="session">JACS:  Geo Json API for Cloud SQL</field><field name="sentence">JACS is an App Engine application that exposes an API for accessing geospatialdata located in  Cloud SQL The API mimics the Google Maps Engine API, and provides a convenient way for your Google Maps API application to fetch data for the Data Layer, withoutneeding to maintain a SQL Database or web server.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6937</field><field name="title">google-jacs</field><field name="session">Deploy</field><field name="sentence">Please see the  Deployment Guide  in the JACS Wiki</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6938</field><field name="title">google-jacs</field><field name="session">Next Steps</field><field name="sentence">You need to populate you Cloud SQL database with geospatial data, and create afront-end application to display your map data</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6939</field><field name="title">google-jacs</field><field name="session">Next Steps</field><field name="sentence">You can host the HTML and javascript in the same App Engine instance.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6940</field><field name="title">google-jacs</field><field name="session">Installing Libraries</field><field name="sentence">See the  Third partylibraries page for libraries that are already included in the SDK</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6941</field><field name="title">google-jacs</field><field name="session">Installing Libraries</field><field name="sentence">To include SDKlibraries, add them in your app.yaml file</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6942</field><field name="title">google-jacs</field><field name="session">Installing Libraries</field><field name="sentence">Other than libraries included inthe SDK, only pure python libraries may be added to an App Engine project.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6943</field><field name="title">google-jacs</field><field name="session">Feedback</field><field name="sentence">Star this repo if you found it useful</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6944</field><field name="title">google-jacs</field><field name="session">Feedback</field><field name="sentence">Use the  github issue tracker to give feedback on JACS.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6945</field><field name="title">google-jacs</field><field name="session">Contributing changes</field><field name="sentence">See  CONTRIB.md  CONTRIB.md</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6946</field><field name="title">google-jacs</field><field name="session">Licensing</field><field name="sentence">See  LICENSE  LICENSE</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6947</field><field name="title">google-jacs</field><field name="session">Not a Google product</field><field name="sentence">This is not an official Google product  experimental or otherwise , it isjust code that happens to be owned by Google.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6948</field><field name="title">google-jarjar</field><field name="session">How does it work?</field><field name="sentence">Jar Jar Links includes an Ant task that extends the built-in jar task</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6949</field><field name="title">google-jarjar</field><field name="session">How does it work?</field><field name="sentence">Thenormal zipfileset element is used to embed jar files</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6950</field><field name="title">google-jarjar</field><field name="session">How does it work?</field><field name="sentence">A new rule element isadded which uses wildcards patterns to rename the embedded class files</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6951</field><field name="title">google-jarjar</field><field name="session">How does it work?</field><field name="sentence">Bytecodetransformation  via ASM  is used to change references to the renamed classes,and special handling is provided for moving resource files and transformingstring literals.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6952</field><field name="title">google-java-monitoring-client-library</field><field name="session">Monitoring Client Library for Java</field><field name="sentence">! BuildStatus  This is not an official Google product.This library provides an API that is powerful and java idiomatic for configuringand publishing application metrics</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6953</field><field name="title">google-java-monitoring-client-library</field><field name="session">Monitoring Client Library for Java</field><field name="sentence">A reference implementation using Stackdriver Monitoring API v3  isincluded, but other monitoring backend implementations can also be used.Most of other monitoring libraries available are low-level and are tied directlyto the backend</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6954</field><field name="title">google-java-monitoring-client-library</field><field name="session">Monitoring Client Library for Java</field><field name="sentence">This library provides type safety, retry logic and anbackend-agnostic approach to Java metrics instrumentation.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6955</field><field name="title">google-java-monitoring-client-library</field><field name="session">Importing the library</field><field name="sentence">The most recent release is  v1.0.3 The Maven group ID is metrics for the main library, and stackdriver for the stackdriver backendwriter</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6956</field><field name="title">google-java-monitoring-client-library</field><field name="session">Importing the library</field><field name="sentence">We also provide a contrib library that is useful if you want to make testassertions on certain metric types with Google's  truth To add a dependency on the metrics library using Maven:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6957</field><field name="title">google-joint_vae</field><field name="session">Variational autoencoder for images and text</field><field name="sentence">Vedantam, Ramakrishna, Ian Fischer, Jonathan Huang, and Kevin Murphy</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6958</field><field name="title">google-joint_vae</field><field name="session">Variational autoencoder for images and text</field><field name="sentence">*Generative Models of Visually Grounded Imagination.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6959</field><field name="title">google-joint_vae</field><field name="session">Usage:</field><field name="sentence">NOTE: All scripts should be run from the root directory of the project.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6960</field><field name="title">google-joint_vae</field><field name="session">Install basic dependencies.</field><field name="sentence">cd to the root directory and run the following command.This sets up the python virtual environment for the project, and downloadsnecessary files for MNIST-A experiments.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6961</field><field name="title">google-joint_vae</field><field name="session">Additional Data Setup</field><field name="sentence">To create your own MNISTA dataset see scripts/create_affine_mnist.sh.Set appropriate paths in datasets/mnist_attributes/affine_mnist_dataset_iid.py and datasets/mnist_attributes/affine_mnist_dataset_comp.py respectively.To download and process CELEBA dataset run scripts/process_and_write_celeba.sh.And set appropriate paths in datasets/celeba/celeba_dataset.py.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6962</field><field name="title">google-joint_vae</field><field name="session">Experiments</field><field name="sentence">If you dont have access to slurm simply run the correspondingpython commands in the above scripts with the appropriate parameters.Example commands to run experiments with slurm:for running experiments  in the above scripts  and run those commands in bash.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6963</field><field name="title">google-joint_vae</field><field name="session">Quantiative Results</field><field name="sentence">See the ipython notebook experiments/iclr_results_aggregate.ipynb on how to viewthe imagination results after running imeval  imagination evaluation  jobs, post</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6964</field><field name="title">google-joint_vae</field><field name="session">Contributors</field><field name="sentence">This project is not an official Google project</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6965</field><field name="title">google-joint_vae</field><field name="session">Contributors</field><field name="sentence">It is not supported by Googleand Google specifically disclaims all warranties as to its quality,merchantability, or fitness for a particular purpose.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6966</field><field name="title">google-joint_vae</field><field name="session">Contributing:</field><field name="sentence">See how to  contribute  ./CONTRIBUTING.md .</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6967</field><field name="title">google-joint_vae</field><field name="session">License:</field><field name="sentence">Apache 2.0  ./LICENSE .</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6968</field><field name="title">google-js-green-licenses</field><field name="session">JavaScript package.json License Checker</field><field name="sentence">! NPM Version  npm-image   npm-url  ! CircleCI  circle-image   circle-url   david-image   david-url   david-dev-image   david-dev-url  ! Known Vulnerabilities  snyk-image   snyk-url  ! codecov  codecov-image   codecov-url  ! Greenkeeper badge  **This is not an official Google product.**This is a tool for checking the license of JavaScript projects</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6969</field><field name="title">google-js-green-licenses</field><field name="session">JavaScript package.json License Checker</field><field name="sentence">It scans thepackage.json file to check its license and recursively checks all of its**DISCLAIMER: This tool is NOT a replacement for legal advice or duediligence for your project's license validity</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6970</field><field name="title">google-js-green-licenses</field><field name="session">JavaScript package.json License Checker</field><field name="sentence">We recommend you consult alawyer if you want legal advice.**</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6971</field><field name="title">google-js-green-licenses</field><field name="session">Installation</field><field name="sentence">usage: jsgl  -h   -v   --local    --pr  License checker for npm modulesPositional arguments:  Optional arguments:  -h, --help  -v, --version  --local , -l   --pr   --dev  --verboseThis tool checks licenses for 1  an already published NPM package, 2  a localdirectory, or 3  a GitHub pull request</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6972</field><field name="title">google-js-green-licenses</field><field name="session">Installation</field><field name="sentence">For checking an NPM package, you canjust pass the package name  optionally together with the version  as theargument</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6973</field><field name="title">google-js-green-licenses</field><field name="session">Installation</field><field name="sentence">To check a local directory, you should pass the --localpath/to/repo argument</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6974</field><field name="title">google-js-green-licenses</field><field name="session">Installation</field><field name="sentence">To check for a GitHub PR, you should pass the --pr//pull/ argument.If the tool finds any non-green licenses in the given package or in itsdependencies, they will be printed out together with the detailedIf you pass dependencies.jsgl also checks sub-packages for --local and --pr flags when itdetects that the repository is a monorepo</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6975</field><field name="title">google-js-green-licenses</field><field name="session">Installation</field><field name="sentence">It assumes a certain directorystructure for detecting whether a repository is a monorepo: the top-leveldirectory should have the packages directory in it and sub-packages mustexist under that directory</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6976</field><field name="title">google-js-green-licenses</field><field name="session">Installation</field><field name="sentence">In that case, all the package.json files arefound from sub-packages and jsgl checks all of them.For example, when a directory , jsgl checks all of foo/package.json, foo/packages/bar/package.json,and foo/packages/baz/package.json.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6977</field><field name="title">google-js-green-licenses</field><field name="session">Configurations</field><field name="sentence">You can customize how greenLicenses section of the configuration file</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6978</field><field name="title">google-js-green-licenses</field><field name="session">Configurations</field><field name="sentence">In that case, jsgl willuse that custom list instead of its default list.The default green license list is:You can also whitelist some NPM packages and they will be considered "green"even when they have non-green licenses or no licenses</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6979</field><field name="title">google-js-green-licenses</field><field name="session">Configurations</field><field name="sentence">It's useful whenpackage.json but has a separate LICENSE file, jsgl can't verify that.You can whitelist that package to make jsgl not complain about thatA typical configuration file looks like this:The packageWhitelist section is for the package whitelist.Note that comments are allowed in js-green-licenses.json.The configuration file must be located in the top-level directory of arepository for jsgl tries to locate the configuration file in the current local directoryfrom which jsgl is invoked.It is desirable that the license names in the greenLicenses section bevalid license IDs defined in  whenever possible.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6980</field><field name="title">google-js-green-licenses</field><field name="session">Interface as a Library</field><field name="sentence">You can also use js-green-licenses as a library as well as a command-lineutility</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6981</field><field name="title">google-js-green-licenses</field><field name="session">Interface as a Library</field><field name="sentence">Usually the LicenseChecker class is the only one you would have to</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6982</field><field name="title">google-js-green-licenses</field><field name="session">Instantiation</field><field name="sentence">generates more verbose output.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6983</field><field name="title">google-js-green-licenses</field><field name="session">Use in Gulp</field><field name="sentence">const jsgl = require 'js-green-licenses' ;gulp.task 'check_licenses', function   {  const checker = new jsgl.LicenseChecker {  } ;  checker.setDefaultHandlers  ;  return checker.checkLocalDirectory '.' ;} ;</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6984</field><field name="title">google-js-green-licenses</field><field name="session">Events</field><field name="sentence">A LicenseChecker object emits following events during its processing</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6985</field><field name="title">google-js-green-licenses</field><field name="session">Events</field><field name="sentence">circle-image :  circle-url :  codecov-image :  codecov-url :  david-dev-image :  david-dev-url :  david-image :  david-url :  npm-image :  npm-url :  snyk-image :  snyk-url :</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6986</field><field name="title">google-jsaction</field><field name="session">JsAction</field><field name="sentence">JsAction is a tiny event delegation library that allows decoupling the DOM nodeson which the action occurs from the JavaScript code that handles the action.The traditional way of adding an event handler is to obtain a reference to thenode and add the event handler to it</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6987</field><field name="title">google-jsaction</field><field name="session">JsAction</field><field name="sentence">JsAction allows us to map between eventsand names of handlers for these events via a custom HTML attribute calledSeparately, JavaScript code registers event handlers with given names which neednot be exposed globally</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6988</field><field name="title">google-jsaction</field><field name="session">JsAction</field><field name="sentence">When an event occurs the name of the action is mappedto the corresponding handler which is executed.Finally, JsAction uncouples event handling from actual implementations</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6989</field><field name="title">google-jsaction</field><field name="session">JsAction</field><field name="sentence">Thus onemay late load the implementations, while the app is always able to respond touser actions marked up through JsAction</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6990</field><field name="title">google-jsaction</field><field name="session">JsAction</field><field name="sentence">This can help in greatly reducing pageload time, in particular for server side rendered apps.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6991</field><field name="title">google-jsaction</field><field name="session">Building</field><field name="sentence">JsAction is built using the  ClosureCompiler  You can obtain a recentcompiler from the site.JsAction depends on the  ClosureLibrary  You can obtain a copy of thelibrary from the GitHub repository.The compiler is able to handle dependency ordering automatically with the--only_closure_dependencies flag</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6992</field><field name="title">google-jsaction</field><field name="session">Building</field><field name="sentence">It needs to be provided with the sources andany entry points.See the files dispatch_auto.js, eventcontract_auto.js, andeventcontract_example.js for typical entry points.Here is a typical command line for building JsAction's dispatch_auto.js:find path/to/closure-library path/to/jsaction -name "*.js" |</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6993</field><field name="title">google-jsaction</field><field name="session">Using drop-in scripts</field><field name="sentence">If you would like to test out JsAction, you can link precompiled scripts intoyour page.</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6994</field><field name="title">google-jsaction</field><field name="session">Usage</field><field name="sentence">You can play around with JsAction already set up with the following directionsat</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6995</field><field name="title">google-jsaction</field><field name="session">In the DOM</field><field name="sentence">Actions are indicated with the jsaction attribute</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6996</field><field name="title">google-jsaction</field><field name="session">In the DOM</field><field name="sentence">They are separated by ;,where each one takes the form:</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6997</field><field name="title">google-jsaction</field><field name="session">Set up</field><field name="sentence">const eventContract = new jsaction.EventContract  ;// Events will be handled for all elements under this container.eventContract.addContainer document.getElementById 'container'  ;// Register the event types we care about.eventContract.addEvent 'click' ;eventContract.addEvent 'dblclick' ;const dispatcher = new jsaction.Dispatcher  ;eventContract.dispatchTo dispatcher.dispatch.bind dispatcher  ;</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6998</field><field name="title">google-jsaction</field><field name="session">Register individual handlers</field><field name="sentence">/*const doStuff = function flow  {  // do stuff  alert 'doStuff called!' ;dispatcher.registerHandlers</field></doc>
<doc><field name="id">6999</field><field name="title">google-jsaction</field><field name="session">Late loading the JsAction dispatcher and event handlers</field><field name="sentence">JsAction splits the event contract and dispatcher into two separably loadablebinaries</field></doc>
